<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS SSO on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-sso/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS SSO on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-sso/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part two, configuring Keycloak as my Identity provider</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-two/</guid>
      <description>This is the follow up post to Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part one, deploying Keycloak on AWS, where I looked at how to deploy Keycloak on AWS in order to have an Identity Provider to use when configuring AWS Identity Centre. In this post, I am going to use that setup, and show you how I configured it to integrate with AWS Identity Centre to provide access to my AWS resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part one, deploying Keycloak on AWS</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-one/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part one, deploying Keycloak on AWS &amp;ldquo;It was the best of times, it was the worst of times&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A Tale of Two Cities&#xA;It started out innocently enough. As part of working on a new blog post, I needed a way to use an open source tool called saml2aws that generates AWS short lived credentials that you can use to access your AWS resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating AWS SSO and G-Suite synchronisation with SSO Sync</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/automating-aws-sso-and-g-suite-synchronisation-with-sso-sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/automating-aws-sso-and-g-suite-synchronisation-with-sso-sync/</guid>
      <description>update-July 28th The ssosync tool has had a lot of interest and the community has updated the tool. This means that you should refer to the project home page https://github.com/awslabs/ssosync and check out the README.md for what changes you might need to make to get this tool working.&#xA;Next level ssosync In a previous post, I talked about setting up AWS Single Sign On (AWS SSO) with G-Suite, and then using an open source project called ssosync to syncronise users and groups from G-Suite into AWS SSO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting up G-Suite, AWS SSO and ssosync</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/setting-up-g-suite-aws-sso-and-ssosync/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/setting-up-g-suite-aws-sso-and-ssosync/</guid>
      <description>update-July 28th The ssosync tool has had a lot of interest and the community has updated the tool. This means that you should refer to the project home page https://github.com/awslabs/ssosync and check out the README.md for what changes you might need to make to get this tool working.&#xA;Enabling AWS SSO with Google G-Suite Many customers have existing directory technologies where they manage their users, and then use this central identity store as a way to simplify the way they authenticate and provide access to applications and other resources.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
