<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Next.js on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/next.js/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Next.js on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/next.js/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #172</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</guid>
      <description>September 4th, 2023 - Instalment #172 Welcome to #172 of the AWS open source newsletter, your reliable source for all open source on AWS goodness. What do we have for you this week? Well, more new projects to check out, and plenty of fresh content on the open source projects you all love.&#xA;We have tools to help you export your DynamoDB tables as csv files, a tool that goes beyond tracking cost and actually shuts down resources to help you manage your AWS budget, a cool dashboard to help you stay on top of your EC2 configurations, a couple of useful utilities to simplify working with files on Amazon S3, and then a sample Cedar project that helps you implement a Lambda authoriser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #170</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-170/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-170/</guid>
      <description>August 21st, 2023 - Instalment #170 Welcome to edition #170 of the AWS open source newsletter, an oasis of open source goodness that features the latest new projects, essential reading, and must view videos to quench the thirst of every open source developer. This weeks edition we have new projects that help you get on top of your IAM actions, a handy tool for knowing what your current AWS account service limits are from the command line, a tool to help you do database migrations, and some interesting and very detailed reference solutions for gaming, live streaming, and managing/exporting of your Amazon Cognito profiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #164</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</guid>
      <description>July 10th, 2023 - Instalment #164 Welcome to #164 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;New projects this week will help you implement single table designs easily on Amazon DynamoDB, an experimental project to help you get to grips with Cedar, a comprehensive clickstream analytics project for your applications, web sites, and mobile applications, and some cool projects to help you with edge and hybrid use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #161</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-161/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-161/</guid>
      <description>June 19th, 2023 - Instalment #161 Welcome to #161 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week for fresh, new open source projects and code for you to practice your four freedoms. This weeks projects include tools that will help you create temporary elevated credentials, a new Java library that provides methods for encrypting and decrypting cryptographic materials, an AWS DynamoDB wrapper for Node/TypeScript developers, and a solution to help you find and visualise data assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #144</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</guid>
      <description>Feb 5th, 2023 - Instalment #144 Welcome to edition #144 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. Some of the treats in store for you this week include &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-shell&amp;rdquo;, a project that provides a cli to your favourite AWS database, &amp;ldquo;precloud&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you catch issues with your configuration before you deploy, &amp;ldquo;node-latency-for-k8s&amp;rdquo; a tool to analyse your node logs, &amp;ldquo;stepfunctions-lambda-ec2-ssm&amp;rdquo; a very nice way of using step functions to overcome the 15 minute timeout of your lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;terraform-ec2-image-builder-container-hardening-pipeline&amp;rdquo; a very cool example of how to build an EC2 image hardening pipeline using Terraform, and &amp;ldquo;cloudtrail-event-fuzzy-viewer&amp;rdquo; a tool to copy your AWS CloudTrail events and then fuzzy search them on the command line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #140</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</guid>
      <description>January 9th, 2023 - Instalment #140 Welcome&#xA;Happy New Year and welcome to the first AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #140. If you have not already checked it out, I put together a short retrospective summary of 2022 in the post, AWS open source newsletter - 2022 in review. There are some interesting facts and figures in there. I am also taking time to collect feedback from readers to help shape where this newsletter goes in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #136</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</guid>
      <description>November 21st, 2022 - Instalment #136 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #136, as featured on the latest episode of Build on Open Source. This week we feature new projects including &amp;ldquo;dynamoit&amp;rdquo; a JavaFX gui for Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;building-apache-kafka-connectors&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;msk-config-providers&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;msk-serverless-data-pipeline&amp;rdquo; projects to help make your life easier when working with Apache Kafka, &amp;ldquo;stowrs-to-s3&amp;rdquo; a tool for working with STOWRS data on AWS, &amp;ldquo;aws-device-lobby&amp;rdquo; a tool to make onboarding devices into AWS IoT Core easier, &amp;ldquo;aws-graviton-run-confidential-ml-workloads-using-nitro-enclaves&amp;rdquo; a nice example of how you can do Confidential Computing for machine learning use cases, &amp;ldquo;aws-hpc-builder&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you manage your open source HPC tools, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
