<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS Amplify on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-amplify/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS Amplify on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-amplify/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #181</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</guid>
      <description>November 27th, 2023 - Instalment #181 Welcome to #181 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As some of you will know, this is re:Invent week, where many of my colleagues and tens of thousands of developers will be congregating to learn about Cloud, and hopefully discover plenty of open source goodness too. If you are going, make sure to visit the open source booth in the Expo floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #180</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-180/</guid>
      <description>November 20th, 2023 - Instalment #180 Welcome to #180 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As we ramp up to re:Invent, it is good to see that pre:Invent is giving us plenty of open source goodies. In this weeks newsletter, we have some of those in the way of new projects such as res and aws-iatk, but we also have lots of really great content too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #176</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</guid>
      <description>October 23rd, 2023 - Instalment #176 Welcome to #176 of the AWS open source newsletter, heading into Autumn and getting ready for the clocks to go back later in the week. How will you use that extra hour? Well, perhaps some of you might use it to check out this weeks new projects, which include a nice cli chat tool that uses Amazon Bedrock, a tool to help simplify deploying VSCode in the Cloud environments, and sample demos and code on chaos engineering, deploying Amazon Bedrock via AWS Lambda, and how you can use IAM Roles Anywhere to authenticate against external identity providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #174</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</guid>
      <description>September 18th, 2023 - Instalment #174 Welcome to #174 of the AWS open source newsletter, which will be the last one for a couple of weeks as I take some time off to recharge. I will be back in early October with more open source goodness, but in the meantime, you still have this edition packed with open source goodness.&#xA;This weeks new projects include a Rust tool to help you keep your CloudFormation stacks up to date, a tool to help upload files to Amazon S3, a generative AI tool that aims to help you review and detect IAM configuration issues, an updated JDBC driver for connecting to Amazon Aurora, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #173</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-173/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-173/</guid>
      <description>September 11th, 2023 - Instalment #173 Welcome to #173 of the AWS open source newsletter, bringing you all the news and latest projects for AWS developers. This weeks new projects include a Golang based SDK for kernel eBPF operations, a project that helps you to optimise your network performance, a couple of projects for Apache Flink users, as well as a handful of different tools and demos featuring open source technologies helping to drive innovation in generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #172</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</guid>
      <description>September 4th, 2023 - Instalment #172 Welcome to #172 of the AWS open source newsletter, your reliable source for all open source on AWS goodness. What do we have for you this week? Well, more new projects to check out, and plenty of fresh content on the open source projects you all love.&#xA;We have tools to help you export your DynamoDB tables as csv files, a tool that goes beyond tracking cost and actually shuts down resources to help you manage your AWS budget, a cool dashboard to help you stay on top of your EC2 configurations, a couple of useful utilities to simplify working with files on Amazon S3, and then a sample Cedar project that helps you implement a Lambda authoriser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #168</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-168/</guid>
      <description>August 7th, 2023 - Instalment #168 Welcome to #168 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only newsletter that features the freshest open source and AWS content*&#xA;New projects for you to feast on in this issue include the obligatory projects that look at how Generative AI can help developers be more productive, in this case by making documentation more relevant and easier to find and to help with code reviews, a nice tool to help you query your AWS Identity Access Management (IAM) policies, and a security focused tool to help you search for potentially incorrect configured S3 buckets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #166</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-166/</guid>
      <description>July 24th, 2023 - Instalment #166 Welcome to #166 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;This weeks new projects include a library to help you managed and validate your environment variables when working with AWS Lambda, a new Rust based tool for interacting with your S3 buckets, an essential tool to help CDK developers remove a lot of the setup work, and a tool that helps you run Yocto embedded Linux build jobs in AWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #164</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</guid>
      <description>July 10th, 2023 - Instalment #164 Welcome to #164 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;New projects this week will help you implement single table designs easily on Amazon DynamoDB, an experimental project to help you get to grips with Cedar, a comprehensive clickstream analytics project for your applications, web sites, and mobile applications, and some cool projects to help you with edge and hybrid use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #163</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</guid>
      <description>July 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #163 Welcome to #163 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week. This weeks featured projects include a Cedar authorisation service and demo examples, a tool to help you find dangling DNS records, a new CLI for those using Amazon ECR, an accelerator for observability on AWS, a serverless web analytics solution (so good, that I implemented it myself), and several more projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #162</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-162/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-162/</guid>
      <description>June 26th, 2023 - Instalment #162 Welcome to #162 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;If you are looking for new projects to try out, then this weeks projects include a very handy tool for Amazon EKS admins, a new experimental project that looks to use ChatGPT to manage your AWS resources, a workshop on Generative AI on AWS, a new tool that helps simplify how you can connect to RDS resources, a PHP library to help you verify your JWT tokens, and a great example application of how you can use Cedar and Amazon Verified Permissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #161</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-161/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-161/</guid>
      <description>June 19th, 2023 - Instalment #161 Welcome to #161 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week for fresh, new open source projects and code for you to practice your four freedoms. This weeks projects include tools that will help you create temporary elevated credentials, a new Java library that provides methods for encrypting and decrypting cryptographic materials, an AWS DynamoDB wrapper for Node/TypeScript developers, and a solution to help you find and visualise data assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #158</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</guid>
      <description>May 30th, 2023 - Instalment #158 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #158. I hope some of you were able to catch the last episode of season two of Build on Open Source where we looked at some of the projects featured in this newsletter (specctl, eksdemo, and ec2-spot-placement-score-tracker). As always we pride ourself on this newsletter on giving you the newest, shiniest open source projects and this week we have some really great ones to share with you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #157</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-157/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-157/</guid>
      <description>May 22nd, 2023 - Instalment #157 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #157. Apologies for the lack of newsletter last week, but hopefully this week will make up for that as we have a bumper selection of great open source content for you. This weeks new projects include repos that help you get OpenEMR up and running (&amp;ldquo;host-openemr-on-aws-fargate&amp;rdquo;), two new security related open source projects that you definitely need to check out, (&amp;ldquo;cedar&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;snapchange&amp;rdquo;), integration of clickstream analytics using Swift (&amp;ldquo;clickstream-swift&amp;rdquo;), deployment of Backstage to serve up access to your AWS resources, (&amp;ldquo;app-development-for-backstage-io-on-aws&amp;rdquo;), a tool to help you clean up ecs tasks definitions (&amp;ldquo;aws-ecs-task-definition-cleanup&amp;rdquo;) and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #156</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-156/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-156/</guid>
      <description>May 8th, 2023 - Instalment #156 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #156, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. So what do we have for you this week? Coming up later in this newsletter we have projects such as &amp;ldquo;sustainability-scanner&amp;rdquo; helps you check your Cloudformation templates against sustainability good practices, &amp;ldquo;synthtable&amp;rdquo; helps you create synthetic data for different use cases, &amp;ldquo;neptune-gremlin-client&amp;rdquo; a Java based Gremlin client, &amp;ldquo;s3zipper&amp;rdquo; a tool to quickly download entire S3 buckets, &amp;ldquo;chataws&amp;rdquo; a nice demo of how you can use ChatGPT to aid your AWS deployments, and plenty of other great projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #154</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-154/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-154/</guid>
      <description>April 24th, 2023 - Instalment #154 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #154, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. We have another great selection of projects for you as always, starting off with &amp;ldquo;cfn-teleport&amp;rdquo; an essential cli tool for Cloudformation users, &amp;ldquo;aither&amp;rdquo; an interesting collaborative development tool using virtualised desktops on containers, &amp;ldquo;tabular-column-semantic-search&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you find similar types of data in your data lakes, &amp;ldquo;resource-lister&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;komiser&amp;rdquo; tools that help you manage your AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;resource-utilization&amp;rdquo; helps you track your AWS resource utilisation, &amp;ldquo;iot-network-traffic-control-and-load-testing-simulator&amp;rdquo; an interesting load and chaos testing example, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #152</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-152/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-152/</guid>
      <description>April 10th, 2023 - Instalment #152 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #152 an Easter special. This week sees more great new projects including, &amp;ldquo;redshift-test-drive&amp;rdquo; a set of essential tools for Amazon Redshift users, &amp;ldquo;simple-database-archival-solution&amp;rdquo; a nice tool to help you archive your data, &amp;ldquo;attribution-gen&amp;rdquo; a Go tool to help you build open source attribution documents, &amp;ldquo;aws-glue-data-catalog-federation&amp;rdquo; a library to help you federate your Glue catalog, &amp;ldquo;subnet-utilization-monitor-for-amazon-vpc&amp;rdquo; a handy tool to keep on top of your IP address allocation, &amp;ldquo;AlexaGPT&amp;rdquo; a demo of integrating Alexa with you know what, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #146</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</guid>
      <description>Feb 27th, 2023 - Instalment #146 Welcome to edition #146 of the AWS open source newsletter. This week we have another great selection of brand new, shiny open source projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. Some of the projects this week include &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-web-adapter&amp;rdquo; that will help you build portable Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;aws-marketplace-cli&amp;rdquo; if you want to escape the GUI when working with AWS Marketplace, this one is for you, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;otel-config-validator&amp;rdquo; helps you sanity check your configuration files, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-openai-chatbot-demo&amp;rdquo; build a personal assistance powered by ChatGPT, &amp;ldquo;drone-video-analysis&amp;rdquo; if you have wanted to use AI services to process your drone video footage, check this project out, &amp;ldquo;mask-words-in-image&amp;rdquo; a nice command line tool to quick mask data based on your needs, and many more cool projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #145</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-145/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-145/</guid>
      <description>Feb 20th, 2023 - Instalment #145 Welcome to edition #145 of the AWS open source newsletter. I hope some of you were able to catch the new Build on Open Source show we live streamed last Friday. You can catch up and replay the session by clicking on this link, where we went over a number of projects from this and a few previous newsletters, and we had special guest Valter who walked us through his project terraform-dev-containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #144</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</guid>
      <description>Feb 5th, 2023 - Instalment #144 Welcome to edition #144 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. Some of the treats in store for you this week include &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-shell&amp;rdquo;, a project that provides a cli to your favourite AWS database, &amp;ldquo;precloud&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you catch issues with your configuration before you deploy, &amp;ldquo;node-latency-for-k8s&amp;rdquo; a tool to analyse your node logs, &amp;ldquo;stepfunctions-lambda-ec2-ssm&amp;rdquo; a very nice way of using step functions to overcome the 15 minute timeout of your lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;terraform-ec2-image-builder-container-hardening-pipeline&amp;rdquo; a very cool example of how to build an EC2 image hardening pipeline using Terraform, and &amp;ldquo;cloudtrail-event-fuzzy-viewer&amp;rdquo; a tool to copy your AWS CloudTrail events and then fuzzy search them on the command line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #139</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</guid>
      <description>December 18th, 2022 - Instalment #139 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the last AWS open source newsletter of 2022, edition #139. I am planning on take a few weeks off to recharge, and wish readers of this newsletter a fabulous Christmas and New Year. Over 100K of you have read this newsletter, so I want to thank you all for your continued support. This newsletter is only possible because of the passion and enthusiasm of open source Builders, and I look forward to seeing what 2023 will bring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #138</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</guid>
      <description>December 12th, 2022 - Instalment #138 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #138. After a week off due to re:Invent, this edition is packed with content on many of the open source related announcements. As always, we have a great line up of new projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. In no particular order, we have projects like &amp;ldquo;eks-node-viewer&amp;rdquo;, a nice visualisation tool for your Amazon EKS clusters, &amp;ldquo;pg_tle&amp;rdquo; a great new project to make your PostgreSQL environments safer, &amp;ldquo;dyna53&amp;rdquo; a fun project that finally turns Amazon Route 53 into a database, &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-mass-migrations&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you migrate to Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;visual-asset-management-system&amp;rdquo; a very nice digital asset management tool, &amp;ldquo;fast-differential-privacy&amp;rdquo; implement differential privacy in your PyTorch models, &amp;ldquo;migration-hadoop-to-emr-tco-simulator&amp;rdquo; a handy total cost of ownership calculator for Amazon EMR, &amp;ldquo;realtime-toxicity-detection&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you stay on top of your online communities, &amp;ldquo;functionclarity&amp;rdquo; a very cool tool to check the integrity of your serverless functions before executing, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #137</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-137/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-137/</guid>
      <description>November 25th, 2022 - Instalment #137 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #137. As it is re:Invent next week, I will be publishing the newsletter early as I am heading out on Monday. I will be in Las Vegas talking with open source Builders, hanging out on the Open Source Kiosk in the AWS Village, and doing some talks. If you are coming, I would love to meet some of you, so get in touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #136</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</guid>
      <description>November 21st, 2022 - Instalment #136 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #136, as featured on the latest episode of Build on Open Source. This week we feature new projects including &amp;ldquo;dynamoit&amp;rdquo; a JavaFX gui for Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;building-apache-kafka-connectors&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;msk-config-providers&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;msk-serverless-data-pipeline&amp;rdquo; projects to help make your life easier when working with Apache Kafka, &amp;ldquo;stowrs-to-s3&amp;rdquo; a tool for working with STOWRS data on AWS, &amp;ldquo;aws-device-lobby&amp;rdquo; a tool to make onboarding devices into AWS IoT Core easier, &amp;ldquo;aws-graviton-run-confidential-ml-workloads-using-nitro-enclaves&amp;rdquo; a nice example of how you can do Confidential Computing for machine learning use cases, &amp;ldquo;aws-hpc-builder&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you manage your open source HPC tools, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #135</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-135/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-135/</guid>
      <description>November 11th, 2022 - Instalment #135 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #135.&#xA;What do we have in store for you in this weeks instalment? I am happy to report that we have yet more great new projects this week. These include &amp;ldquo;sovereign-keys&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;nitrogen&amp;rdquo; are new projects to help you secure and get started working with enclaves, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-scheduler&amp;rdquo; helps you schedule your events, &amp;ldquo;aws-resource-explorer-cli&amp;rdquo; provides a command line tool for this new capability, &amp;ldquo;workload-discovery-on-aws&amp;rdquo; helps you stay on top of your AWS workloads, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;image-content-moderation&amp;rdquo; provide a sample project for image moderation you can integrate into your workflows, &amp;ldquo;cloudenv&amp;rdquo; is a proof of concept that explores managing secrets and prameters, &amp;ldquo;cdk-schema-watcher&amp;rdquo; is a tool to help you stay notified of schema changes in your event driven applications, and several other projects to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #132</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</guid>
      <description>October 21st, 2022 - Instalment #132 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #132. This newsletter was covered in last Friday&amp;rsquo;s Build on Open Source, so if you missed it, don&amp;rsquo;t worry as you can view episode five of Build on Open Source. In this episode special guest Abhishek Gupta walked us through how to use cdk8s using Golang, building a Wordpress site in minutes.&#xA;New projects this week include &amp;ldquo;duvet&amp;rdquo; a tool to help honour RFC in code, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-explorer&amp;rdquo; a gui tool to explore your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;k3s-aws-terraform-cluster&amp;rdquo; deploy k3s on AWS via Terraform, &amp;ldquo;snow-transfer-tool&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you transfer data via Snowball devices, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-vscode-toolkit&amp;rdquo; a new VSCode plugin for Amazon EMR users, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-for-discourse&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy the open source discourse tool, &amp;ldquo;image-optimization&amp;rdquo; a reference example of how to do image optimising, and &amp;ldquo;gtfs-serverless-ticketing-sample&amp;rdquo; a sample application using public transport data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #116</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-116/</guid>
      <description>June 10th, 2022 - Instalment #116 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #116.&#xA;Another selection of useful and interesting new open source projects for you to try out this week. First up, we have &amp;ldquo;aws-exec&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you do adhoc shell execution in AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;edgy&amp;rdquo; helps you simplify writing tests for Node.js based AWS CloudFront Lambda@Edge functions, &amp;ldquo;cdk-app-cli&amp;rdquo; a really nice cli that every AWS CDK user should know about, &amp;ldquo;Accumulus&amp;rdquo; a great looking reporting tool for AWS Lambda users, &amp;ldquo;sqldef-gitops-cdk&amp;rdquo; is a schema management for several open source databases, &amp;ldquo;log-hub&amp;rdquo; helps you to build your own log analytics tool using OpenSearch, &amp;ldquo;verifiable-controls-evidence-store&amp;rdquo; a very cool solution that builds a mechanism to centrally store findings and results of cloud security controls governing AWS workloads, and many more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #115</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-115/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-115/</guid>
      <description>June 3rd, 2022 - Instalment #115 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #115.&#xA;This week we have another great selection of brand new open source projects for you to explore, including &amp;ldquo;firec&amp;rdquo; a Rust client library for interacting with Firecracker, &amp;ldquo;sfn-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool that helps you quickly build StepFunctions definitions, &amp;ldquo;ssm-cloner&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you replicate across AWS regions your AWS System Manager documents, &amp;ldquo;amazon-lambda-compute-tuning&amp;rdquo; an AWS Lambda function benchmarking tool, &amp;ldquo;aws-iam-root-user-activity-monitor&amp;rdquo; a sample project to help you keep track of your root user, &amp;ldquo;hpc-cost-simulator&amp;rdquo; a tool to help estimate costs running your HPC workloads on AWS, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #114</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-114/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-114/</guid>
      <description>May 27th, 2022 - Instalment #114 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter #114. This weeks new open source projects feature a variety of community related projects such as &amp;ldquo;instance-scheduler&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you schedule AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;libaws&amp;rdquo; an opinionated tool that helps you simplify creation and deletion of some AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;elasticspot&amp;rdquo; a nice tool to help you reassign elastic IPs, and &amp;ldquo;auto-close-aws-accounts&amp;rdquo; that allows you to close AWS accounts if you are using AWS Organisations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #108</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-108/</guid>
      <description>April 11th, 2022 - Instalment #108 Newsletter #108.&#xA;A little later the usual as it was a busy week last week, and I was lucky enough to speak at some great events. It certainly seems that things are returning to normality now on the tech events scene, and it was great to meet so many customers and builders who were enthusiastic champions of open source. The AWS Summit season is upon us, with the Brussels summit just gone and Paris Summit happening this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #106</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-106/</guid>
      <description>March 28th, 2022 - Instalment #106 Newsletter #106.&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, and this week we have more great new open source projects to tell you about. We have &amp;ldquo;access-undenied-aws&amp;rdquo;, a tool that helps you better understand your CloudTrail logs and suggest remediation. &amp;ldquo;aws-slack-clickoops-watcher&amp;rdquo; provides you with a way to alert you when changes are made to your AWS environment. &amp;ldquo;kronicle&amp;rdquo; provides a way of illustrating your tech stack automagically, and we have many more tools, demos and sample projects to help get you started on a number of topics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #101</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-101/</guid>
      <description>Feb 21st, 2022 - Instalment #101 Newsletter #101.&#xA;There is nothing basic and fundamental about edition 101 of the AWS open source newsletter, with another great round up of new open source projects including eks-creation-engine from the folks at Lightspin helping you all to stay safer with this handy tool you should check out, idp-scim-sync to help users of AWS SSO who want to synchronise with their Google Workspace Directory, typecart an analysis tool for proof evolution and many other great projects and sample code.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
