<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS Distro for OpenTelemetry on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-distro-for-opentelemetry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS Distro for OpenTelemetry on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-distro-for-opentelemetry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #182</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-182/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-182/</guid>
      <description>December 11th, 2023 - Instalment #182 Welcome to #182 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This is a special re:Invent packed edition of this newsletter, attempting to catch up and cover all the main talking points, sessions, and announcements. Whilst there is a lot of content to go through, I know that many of you will still be wanting to know about new projects you can try out, and the good news is that we have plenty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #176</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</guid>
      <description>October 23rd, 2023 - Instalment #176 Welcome to #176 of the AWS open source newsletter, heading into Autumn and getting ready for the clocks to go back later in the week. How will you use that extra hour? Well, perhaps some of you might use it to check out this weeks new projects, which include a nice cli chat tool that uses Amazon Bedrock, a tool to help simplify deploying VSCode in the Cloud environments, and sample demos and code on chaos engineering, deploying Amazon Bedrock via AWS Lambda, and how you can use IAM Roles Anywhere to authenticate against external identity providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #164</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</guid>
      <description>July 10th, 2023 - Instalment #164 Welcome to #164 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;New projects this week will help you implement single table designs easily on Amazon DynamoDB, an experimental project to help you get to grips with Cedar, a comprehensive clickstream analytics project for your applications, web sites, and mobile applications, and some cool projects to help you with edge and hybrid use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #157</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-157/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-157/</guid>
      <description>May 22nd, 2023 - Instalment #157 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #157. Apologies for the lack of newsletter last week, but hopefully this week will make up for that as we have a bumper selection of great open source content for you. This weeks new projects include repos that help you get OpenEMR up and running (&amp;ldquo;host-openemr-on-aws-fargate&amp;rdquo;), two new security related open source projects that you definitely need to check out, (&amp;ldquo;cedar&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;snapchange&amp;rdquo;), integration of clickstream analytics using Swift (&amp;ldquo;clickstream-swift&amp;rdquo;), deployment of Backstage to serve up access to your AWS resources, (&amp;ldquo;app-development-for-backstage-io-on-aws&amp;rdquo;), a tool to help you clean up ecs tasks definitions (&amp;ldquo;aws-ecs-task-definition-cleanup&amp;rdquo;) and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #143</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</guid>
      <description>January 30th, 2023 - Instalment #143 Welcome to edition #143 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. This week we feature projects including &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-in-electron&amp;rdquo;, a project that lets you put AWS CDK in a graphical user interface, &amp;ldquo;lightsail-k8s-installer&amp;rdquo; that helps you deploy Kubernetes into Amazon Lightsail, &amp;ldquo;porting-advisor-for-graviton&amp;rdquo; a great project to help you migrate to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, &amp;ldquo;aws-ebook-downloader&amp;rdquo; a browser tool to help you easily download pdf&amp;rsquo;s on AWS topics, &amp;ldquo;lake-formation-permissions-sync&amp;rdquo; a useful tool to help you keep on top of your Lake Formation setups, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #140</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</guid>
      <description>January 9th, 2023 - Instalment #140 Welcome&#xA;Happy New Year and welcome to the first AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #140. If you have not already checked it out, I put together a short retrospective summary of 2022 in the post, AWS open source newsletter - 2022 in review. There are some interesting facts and figures in there. I am also taking time to collect feedback from readers to help shape where this newsletter goes in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #134</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</guid>
      <description>November 7th, 2022 - Instalment #134 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #134. This weeks newsletter was featured in the latest Build on Open Source on twitch.tv/aws, so I hope some of you were able to tune in and watch.&#xA;New projects that we featured include &amp;ldquo;enclaver&amp;rdquo;, a toolkit to make working with enclaves easier, &amp;ldquo;s3crets_scanner&amp;rdquo; a new secrets scanning tool, &amp;ldquo;sandbox-accounts-for-events&amp;rdquo; a way to easily vend temporary environments, &amp;ldquo;frontend-discovery&amp;rdquo; helps you define and drive adoption of a frontend discovery patterns, &amp;ldquo;cf-sam-openapi-file-organization-demo&amp;rdquo;, a tool to help you get started with API development, &amp;ldquo;decoupling-microservices-lambda-amazonmq-rabbitmq&amp;rdquo; a sample solution to get you started on how to use micro services with RabbitMQ, &amp;ldquo;how-to-write-more-correct-software-workshop&amp;rdquo; a workshop to get you developing better software, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #127</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</guid>
      <description>September 16th, 2022 - Instalment #127 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #127. I hope some of you were able to catch Derek and myself sharing a peek at this edition, and enjoyed as our special guest, AWS Hero Ian Mckay walked us through some of his open source projects. It was very cool indeed, and if you have not yet watched, Ian shares an early glimpse of a new project - so make sure you check that out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #114</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-114/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-114/</guid>
      <description>May 27th, 2022 - Instalment #114 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter #114. This weeks new open source projects feature a variety of community related projects such as &amp;ldquo;instance-scheduler&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you schedule AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;libaws&amp;rdquo; an opinionated tool that helps you simplify creation and deletion of some AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;elasticspot&amp;rdquo; a nice tool to help you reassign elastic IPs, and &amp;ldquo;auto-close-aws-accounts&amp;rdquo; that allows you to close AWS accounts if you are using AWS Organisations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #111</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-111/</guid>
      <description>May 6th, 2022 - Instalment #111 Newsletter #111.&#xA;Welcome to edition #111 of the AWS open source newsletter, a bit later this week but that was so I could pack in even more great open source content. This week we have another round up of new open source projects from the AWS community that include tools to help you manage your AWS CloudFront distributions, resource providers for CloudFormation for Confluent users, managing Amazon Route53 via the command line, a nice tool for Rust developers working with AWS Lambda, a nice tool to help you find your CIDR address ranges, and many more including some great samples.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
