<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DJL on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/djl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DJL on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/djl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #159</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-159/</guid>
      <description>June 5th, 2023 - Instalment #159 Welcome to #159 of the AWS open source newsletter, where we try and share all the important open source news, projects, events, and content that open source builders want. This week we have new projects that include tools to help you generate test data, an accelerator for stable diffusion, tools to help you with managing application credentials and variables, a new connector for Apache Kafka, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #154</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-154/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-154/</guid>
      <description>April 24th, 2023 - Instalment #154 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #154, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. We have another great selection of projects for you as always, starting off with &amp;ldquo;cfn-teleport&amp;rdquo; an essential cli tool for Cloudformation users, &amp;ldquo;aither&amp;rdquo; an interesting collaborative development tool using virtualised desktops on containers, &amp;ldquo;tabular-column-semantic-search&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you find similar types of data in your data lakes, &amp;ldquo;resource-lister&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;komiser&amp;rdquo; tools that help you manage your AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;resource-utilization&amp;rdquo; helps you track your AWS resource utilisation, &amp;ldquo;iot-network-traffic-control-and-load-testing-simulator&amp;rdquo; an interesting load and chaos testing example, and more!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
