<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Babelfish for PostgreSQL on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/babelfish-for-postgresql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Babelfish for PostgreSQL on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/babelfish-for-postgresql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #129</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</guid>
      <description>September 30th, 2022 - Instalment #129 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #129.&#xA;We have loads of great new projects this week, with plenty of variety to keep you all interested. We have &amp;ldquo;aws-ecr-cleaner&amp;rdquo;, a great tool to help you manage your container images, &amp;ldquo;dotnet-lambda-sql-server-proxy&amp;rdquo; that shows you how you can use RDS Proxy with SQL Server and why, &amp;ldquo;minecraft-server-dashboard&amp;rdquo; perfect for those running their own minecraft servers, &amp;ldquo;YATAS&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;aws-security-survival-kit&amp;rdquo; for those working on security and governance, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-handler-cookbook&amp;rdquo; useful recipes to get you going, &amp;ldquo;autonomous-driving-data-framework&amp;rdquo; for folks working in the automotive space, and many more - make sure you check all the projects out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #126</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-126/</guid>
      <description>September 9th, 2022 - Instalment #126 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #126. Exciting news this week includes the second episode of the Build on AWS open source show, and the release of a new AWS open source project, event-ruler (more in a bit).&#xA;As always, this weeks newsletter includes more great new open source projects from AWS and the AWS Community. We have &amp;ldquo;aws-integration-for-apache-guacamole&amp;rdquo; that provides a guide of how you can deploy this open source project, &amp;ldquo;xcodeinstall&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you heedlessly install Xcode, &amp;ldquo;soci-snapshotter&amp;rdquo; a very cool project for Container lovers, &amp;ldquo;credentials-fetcher&amp;rdquo; a new Linux demon for those wanting to integrate with Windows environments, &amp;ldquo;imds-credential-server&amp;rdquo; a very nice tool to help you vend AWS credentials, &amp;ldquo;automated-data-analytics-on-aws&amp;rdquo; a new data tool that will help you accelerate time to insights, and &amp;ldquo;event-ruler&amp;rdquo; a very cool new project allowing you to match Rules to Events, and many other projects for you to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #118</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-118/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-118/</guid>
      <description>June 24th, 2022 - Instalment #118 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #118.&#xA;This week we feature more new open source projects, such as &amp;ldquo;seed-farmer&amp;rdquo;, and orchestration tool modelled after GitOps deployments, &amp;ldquo;aws-proton-plugins-for-backstage&amp;rdquo; Backstage plugins for interacting with AWS Proton, &amp;ldquo;dcv-gnome-shell-extension&amp;rdquo; is a GNOME Shell extension to provide functionalities required by NICE DCV, &amp;ldquo;simpleiot-arduino&amp;rdquo; an Arduino library to integrate with the SimpleIOT framework, &amp;ldquo;event-driven-weather-forecasts&amp;rdquo; an event driven weather forecasting demo, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
