<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bottlerocket on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/bottlerocket/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bottlerocket on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/bottlerocket/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #177</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-177/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-177/</guid>
      <description>October 30th, 2023 - Instalment #177 Welcome to #177 of the AWS open source newsletter, the Halloween special. You will find no tricks in this edition, only treats, with more new projects for you to check out and content that are a feast for your eyes. This weeks new projects include a tool to help you easily deploy vector databases on Kubernetes, an observability toolkit, a tool to help you benchmark network latency, as well as lots of new demos on generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #168</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-168/</guid>
      <description>August 7th, 2023 - Instalment #168 Welcome to #168 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only newsletter that features the freshest open source and AWS content*&#xA;New projects for you to feast on in this issue include the obligatory projects that look at how Generative AI can help developers be more productive, in this case by making documentation more relevant and easier to find and to help with code reviews, a nice tool to help you query your AWS Identity Access Management (IAM) policies, and a security focused tool to help you search for potentially incorrect configured S3 buckets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #151</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-151/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-151/</guid>
      <description>April 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #151 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #151. This week sees more great new projects, including those covered in the latest episode of Build on Open Source, such as &amp;ldquo;ec2-former2&amp;rdquo; a way to host this great project to reverse engineer your CloudFormation templates, &amp;ldquo;protonizer&amp;rdquo; a cli tool for those using AWS Proton, &amp;ldquo;fortuna&amp;rdquo;, a library for Uncertainty Quantification, &amp;ldquo;aws-resilience-hub-tools&amp;rdquo; a set of tools and scripts for working with the AWS Resilience Hub, &amp;ldquo;jenkins-unity-build-on-aws&amp;rdquo; a nice reference solution for those needing to build Unity projects, &amp;ldquo;amazon-cognito-passwordless-auth&amp;rdquo; a nice demo of how to do authentication sans password, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #144</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</guid>
      <description>Feb 5th, 2023 - Instalment #144 Welcome to edition #144 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. Some of the treats in store for you this week include &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-shell&amp;rdquo;, a project that provides a cli to your favourite AWS database, &amp;ldquo;precloud&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you catch issues with your configuration before you deploy, &amp;ldquo;node-latency-for-k8s&amp;rdquo; a tool to analyse your node logs, &amp;ldquo;stepfunctions-lambda-ec2-ssm&amp;rdquo; a very nice way of using step functions to overcome the 15 minute timeout of your lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;terraform-ec2-image-builder-container-hardening-pipeline&amp;rdquo; a very cool example of how to build an EC2 image hardening pipeline using Terraform, and &amp;ldquo;cloudtrail-event-fuzzy-viewer&amp;rdquo; a tool to copy your AWS CloudTrail events and then fuzzy search them on the command line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #139</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</guid>
      <description>December 18th, 2022 - Instalment #139 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the last AWS open source newsletter of 2022, edition #139. I am planning on take a few weeks off to recharge, and wish readers of this newsletter a fabulous Christmas and New Year. Over 100K of you have read this newsletter, so I want to thank you all for your continued support. This newsletter is only possible because of the passion and enthusiasm of open source Builders, and I look forward to seeing what 2023 will bring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #132</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</guid>
      <description>October 21st, 2022 - Instalment #132 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #132. This newsletter was covered in last Friday&amp;rsquo;s Build on Open Source, so if you missed it, don&amp;rsquo;t worry as you can view episode five of Build on Open Source. In this episode special guest Abhishek Gupta walked us through how to use cdk8s using Golang, building a Wordpress site in minutes.&#xA;New projects this week include &amp;ldquo;duvet&amp;rdquo; a tool to help honour RFC in code, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-explorer&amp;rdquo; a gui tool to explore your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;k3s-aws-terraform-cluster&amp;rdquo; deploy k3s on AWS via Terraform, &amp;ldquo;snow-transfer-tool&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you transfer data via Snowball devices, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-vscode-toolkit&amp;rdquo; a new VSCode plugin for Amazon EMR users, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-for-discourse&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy the open source discourse tool, &amp;ldquo;image-optimization&amp;rdquo; a reference example of how to do image optimising, and &amp;ldquo;gtfs-serverless-ticketing-sample&amp;rdquo; a sample application using public transport data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #129</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</guid>
      <description>September 30th, 2022 - Instalment #129 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #129.&#xA;We have loads of great new projects this week, with plenty of variety to keep you all interested. We have &amp;ldquo;aws-ecr-cleaner&amp;rdquo;, a great tool to help you manage your container images, &amp;ldquo;dotnet-lambda-sql-server-proxy&amp;rdquo; that shows you how you can use RDS Proxy with SQL Server and why, &amp;ldquo;minecraft-server-dashboard&amp;rdquo; perfect for those running their own minecraft servers, &amp;ldquo;YATAS&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;aws-security-survival-kit&amp;rdquo; for those working on security and governance, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-handler-cookbook&amp;rdquo; useful recipes to get you going, &amp;ldquo;autonomous-driving-data-framework&amp;rdquo; for folks working in the automotive space, and many more - make sure you check all the projects out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #125</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-125/</guid>
      <description>September 2nd, 2022 - Instalment #125 Welcome&#xA;After a couple of weeks off, it is great to welcome to back to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #125. As it has been a couple of weeks, this edition contains even more open source goodness to keep you occupied.&#xA;As always, we kick things off we a round up of new open source projects. Over the past couple of weeks, there were so many that it was hard to select them (I will include the others in next weeks newsletter).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #117</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-117/</guid>
      <description>June 17th, 2022 - Instalment #117 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #117.&#xA;A little behind schedule this week, as I have been speaking at a couple of events this week. It has been good to get back on the stage and to talk and engage with real people. It seems that things are quickly returning back to normal. So this week we have some great new projects for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #104</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-104/</guid>
      <description>March 14th, 2022 - Instalment #104 Newsletter #104.&#xA;Welcome to #104 of the AWS open source news and updates newsletter, bringing you the latest updates from around the AWS and Communities. This week we have yet more great new open source projects, including a Deno runtime for your Lambda functions, data lineage and data testing tools, a performance testing tool for Apache Kafka, an ELT tool for Amazon Redshift, an Amazon S3 archive tool, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
