<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kyber on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/kyber/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kyber on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/kyber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #123</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</guid>
      <description>August, 5th, 2022 - Instalment #123 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter episode #123.&#xA;I sometimes speak with builders who are experienced developers but perhaps new to open source. A common question I get asked is what the impact of them working on open source might be on their careers. Whilst it is never a guarantee, open source can be a great career accelerator. I was reminded of that last week when reading the excellent post from Ran Isenberg, who shared his experience in his post How One Open-Source Code Donation Got Me Promoted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #120</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-120/</guid>
      <description>July 15th, 2022 - Instalment #120 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #120.&#xA;The observant will have noticed that it has been two weeks since the last newsletter. We all need some time off, and I spent most of the time cycling around the hills of a new cycle route called King Alfreds Way - highly recommended.&#xA;There has been some great new projects created over the past couple of weeks, and of course I have you covered and have shared them below.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
