<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apache CloudStack on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/apache-cloudstack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apache CloudStack on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/apache-cloudstack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #141</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</guid>
      <description>January 16th, 2023 - Instalment #141 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #141.&#xA;This week we have more new projects for you to practice your four freedoms, including &amp;ldquo;distributed-compute-on-aws-with-cross-regional-dask&amp;rdquo;, a solution to simplify distributed compute using Dask, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-serverless-image-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool to verify your Amazon EMR custom container images, &amp;ldquo;serverless-run-watch&amp;rdquo; a tool to help accelerate your local development if you are using the Serverless Framework, &amp;ldquo;aws-sso-auto-expand-accounts&amp;rdquo; a quick browser extension for those using AWS SSO, &amp;ldquo;basti&amp;rdquo; a cool Bastion Host alternative, &amp;ldquo;klotho&amp;rdquo; generate cloud native code from your code, &amp;ldquo;amazon-route53-hosted-zone-sync&amp;rdquo; a nice solution for hybrid DNS use cases, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #133</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-133/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-133/</guid>
      <description>October 28th, 2022 - Instalment #133 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #133. This week has been all about KubeCon, and there were some important announcements from AWS. If you missed these, I have tried to capture the important ones here, but I want to start off with probably my favourite which was the announcement during Nate Taber keynote on some of the investments we are providing to CNCF and OpenSSF.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
