<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amazon Linux on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/amazon-linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon Linux on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/amazon-linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #169</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</guid>
      <description>August 14th, 2023 - Instalment #169 Welcome to #169 of the AWS open source newsletter, featuring the latest and greatest open source news, projects, videos, and community content that you need to know about. Featured in this weeks edition we have more great projects, including a new ODBC driver for Amazon Timestream database, a nice tool to simplify your ssh tunnelling, an essential VSCode extension for working with Cedar policies, a couple of projects that help you shift left and validate / monitor your policies, a solution to help you monitor your Apache Kafka environments, as well as some great sample applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #163</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</guid>
      <description>July 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #163 Welcome to #163 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week. This weeks featured projects include a Cedar authorisation service and demo examples, a tool to help you find dangling DNS records, a new CLI for those using Amazon ECR, an accelerator for observability on AWS, a serverless web analytics solution (so good, that I implemented it myself), and several more projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #149</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-149/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-149/</guid>
      <description>March 20th, 2023 - Instalment #149 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to edition #149 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only newsletter on the planet that serves you up a weekly dose of the freshest, latest open source projects on AWS. I hope some of you were able to catch this episode reviewed on our last Build on Open Source livestream. If not, you can catch the replay here. This week we have projects such &amp;ldquo;mountpoint-s3&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;s3-access-for-squash&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;amazon-s3-tar-tool&amp;rdquo; which provide some useful tools for managing your files on S3, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-ai-stories&amp;rdquo; a creative masterclass in storytelling, &amp;ldquo;earthquake-notifier&amp;rdquo; a serverless solution to keep you alerted and ready, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #136</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</guid>
      <description>November 21st, 2022 - Instalment #136 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #136, as featured on the latest episode of Build on Open Source. This week we feature new projects including &amp;ldquo;dynamoit&amp;rdquo; a JavaFX gui for Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;building-apache-kafka-connectors&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;msk-config-providers&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;msk-serverless-data-pipeline&amp;rdquo; projects to help make your life easier when working with Apache Kafka, &amp;ldquo;stowrs-to-s3&amp;rdquo; a tool for working with STOWRS data on AWS, &amp;ldquo;aws-device-lobby&amp;rdquo; a tool to make onboarding devices into AWS IoT Core easier, &amp;ldquo;aws-graviton-run-confidential-ml-workloads-using-nitro-enclaves&amp;rdquo; a nice example of how you can do Confidential Computing for machine learning use cases, &amp;ldquo;aws-hpc-builder&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you manage your open source HPC tools, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
