<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ray on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/ray/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ray on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/ray/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #176</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</guid>
      <description>October 23rd, 2023 - Instalment #176 Welcome to #176 of the AWS open source newsletter, heading into Autumn and getting ready for the clocks to go back later in the week. How will you use that extra hour? Well, perhaps some of you might use it to check out this weeks new projects, which include a nice cli chat tool that uses Amazon Bedrock, a tool to help simplify deploying VSCode in the Cloud environments, and sample demos and code on chaos engineering, deploying Amazon Bedrock via AWS Lambda, and how you can use IAM Roles Anywhere to authenticate against external identity providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #174</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</guid>
      <description>September 18th, 2023 - Instalment #174 Welcome to #174 of the AWS open source newsletter, which will be the last one for a couple of weeks as I take some time off to recharge. I will be back in early October with more open source goodness, but in the meantime, you still have this edition packed with open source goodness.&#xA;This weeks new projects include a Rust tool to help you keep your CloudFormation stacks up to date, a tool to help upload files to Amazon S3, a generative AI tool that aims to help you review and detect IAM configuration issues, an updated JDBC driver for connecting to Amazon Aurora, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #160</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-160/</guid>
      <description>June 12th, 2023 - Instalment #160 Welcome to #160 of the AWS open source newsletter, where we try and share all the important open source news, projects, events, and content that open source builders want. This week we have new projects that include tools to help you build data workflows, Terraform modules to help you incorporate temporary elevated access controls, integrating Tailscale to change your traffic flows, a neat AWS Lambda debugging tool, Go bindings for Cedar, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #141</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</guid>
      <description>January 16th, 2023 - Instalment #141 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #141.&#xA;This week we have more new projects for you to practice your four freedoms, including &amp;ldquo;distributed-compute-on-aws-with-cross-regional-dask&amp;rdquo;, a solution to simplify distributed compute using Dask, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-serverless-image-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool to verify your Amazon EMR custom container images, &amp;ldquo;serverless-run-watch&amp;rdquo; a tool to help accelerate your local development if you are using the Serverless Framework, &amp;ldquo;aws-sso-auto-expand-accounts&amp;rdquo; a quick browser extension for those using AWS SSO, &amp;ldquo;basti&amp;rdquo; a cool Bastion Host alternative, &amp;ldquo;klotho&amp;rdquo; generate cloud native code from your code, &amp;ldquo;amazon-route53-hosted-zone-sync&amp;rdquo; a nice solution for hybrid DNS use cases, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #138</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</guid>
      <description>December 12th, 2022 - Instalment #138 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #138. After a week off due to re:Invent, this edition is packed with content on many of the open source related announcements. As always, we have a great line up of new projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. In no particular order, we have projects like &amp;ldquo;eks-node-viewer&amp;rdquo;, a nice visualisation tool for your Amazon EKS clusters, &amp;ldquo;pg_tle&amp;rdquo; a great new project to make your PostgreSQL environments safer, &amp;ldquo;dyna53&amp;rdquo; a fun project that finally turns Amazon Route 53 into a database, &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-mass-migrations&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you migrate to Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;visual-asset-management-system&amp;rdquo; a very nice digital asset management tool, &amp;ldquo;fast-differential-privacy&amp;rdquo; implement differential privacy in your PyTorch models, &amp;ldquo;migration-hadoop-to-emr-tco-simulator&amp;rdquo; a handy total cost of ownership calculator for Amazon EMR, &amp;ldquo;realtime-toxicity-detection&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you stay on top of your online communities, &amp;ldquo;functionclarity&amp;rdquo; a very cool tool to check the integrity of your serverless functions before executing, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #132</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</guid>
      <description>October 21st, 2022 - Instalment #132 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #132. This newsletter was covered in last Friday&amp;rsquo;s Build on Open Source, so if you missed it, don&amp;rsquo;t worry as you can view episode five of Build on Open Source. In this episode special guest Abhishek Gupta walked us through how to use cdk8s using Golang, building a Wordpress site in minutes.&#xA;New projects this week include &amp;ldquo;duvet&amp;rdquo; a tool to help honour RFC in code, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-explorer&amp;rdquo; a gui tool to explore your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;k3s-aws-terraform-cluster&amp;rdquo; deploy k3s on AWS via Terraform, &amp;ldquo;snow-transfer-tool&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you transfer data via Snowball devices, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-vscode-toolkit&amp;rdquo; a new VSCode plugin for Amazon EMR users, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-for-discourse&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy the open source discourse tool, &amp;ldquo;image-optimization&amp;rdquo; a reference example of how to do image optimising, and &amp;ldquo;gtfs-serverless-ticketing-sample&amp;rdquo; a sample application using public transport data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #125</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-125/</guid>
      <description>September 2nd, 2022 - Instalment #125 Welcome&#xA;After a couple of weeks off, it is great to welcome to back to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #125. As it has been a couple of weeks, this edition contains even more open source goodness to keep you occupied.&#xA;As always, we kick things off we a round up of new open source projects. Over the past couple of weeks, there were so many that it was hard to select them (I will include the others in next weeks newsletter).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #120</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-120/</guid>
      <description>July 15th, 2022 - Instalment #120 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #120.&#xA;The observant will have noticed that it has been two weeks since the last newsletter. We all need some time off, and I spent most of the time cycling around the hills of a new cycle route called King Alfreds Way - highly recommended.&#xA;There has been some great new projects created over the past couple of weeks, and of course I have you covered and have shared them below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #111</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-111/</guid>
      <description>May 6th, 2022 - Instalment #111 Newsletter #111.&#xA;Welcome to edition #111 of the AWS open source newsletter, a bit later this week but that was so I could pack in even more great open source content. This week we have another round up of new open source projects from the AWS community that include tools to help you manage your AWS CloudFront distributions, resource providers for CloudFormation for Confluent users, managing Amazon Route53 via the command line, a nice tool for Rust developers working with AWS Lambda, a nice tool to help you find your CIDR address ranges, and many more including some great samples.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
