<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CDK on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/cdk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CDK on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/cdk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part two, configuring Keycloak as my Identity provider</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-two/</guid>
      <description>This is the follow up post to Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part one, deploying Keycloak on AWS, where I looked at how to deploy Keycloak on AWS in order to have an Identity Provider to use when configuring AWS Identity Centre. In this post, I am going to use that setup, and show you how I configured it to integrate with AWS Identity Centre to provide access to my AWS resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using CDK to deploy AWS managed Active Directory</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/active-directory-using-cdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/active-directory-using-cdk/</guid>
      <description>CIFS (Common Internet File System) and SMB (Server Message Block) are both Windows file-sharing protocols used in storage systems. As part of a new demo/blog post that looks at how to use data stored on SMB/CIF file shares with Apache Airflow, I have been exploring the various options of creating SMB/CIF compatible resources. (There are LOTS of ways you could do this, so there is plenty for me to play around with!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part one, deploying Keycloak on AWS</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/keycloak-on-aws-part-one/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Keycloak as my Identity Provider for IAM Identity Centre: Part one, deploying Keycloak on AWS &amp;ldquo;It was the best of times, it was the worst of times&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; A Tale of Two Cities&#xA;It started out innocently enough. As part of working on a new blog post, I needed a way to use an open source tool called saml2aws that generates AWS short lived credentials that you can use to access your AWS resources.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
