<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubuntu on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/ubuntu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ubuntu on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/ubuntu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #155</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-155/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-155/</guid>
      <description>May 1st, 2023 - Instalment #155 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #155, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. This week&amp;rsquo;s new projects include&#xA;&amp;ldquo;aws-cloudformation-controller-for-flux&amp;rdquo; provides a way to use flux to orchestrate your CloudFormation deployments, &amp;ldquo;threat-composer&amp;rdquo; is a nice React based tool to help you create Threat Models for your systems and applications, &amp;ldquo;cdk-integ-tests-sample&amp;rdquo; a tool to allow you to do integration tests with your CDK stacks (these three were all featured in the latest episode of Build on Open Source, you can watch it here), &amp;ldquo;iam-access-key-report&amp;rdquo; generates reports from your AWS accounts about your AWS access keys, &amp;ldquo;personalize-kafka-connector&amp;rdquo; provides an integration into Apache Kafka for this AWS service, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #147</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-147/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-147/</guid>
      <description>March 6th, 2023 - Instalment #147 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to edition #147 of the AWS open source newsletter, featured in the latest episode of Build on Open Source. This week we have new projects such as &amp;ldquo;metahub&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;savings-estimator&amp;rdquo; that we looked at in closer detail on the Build on Open Source livestream, &amp;ldquo;aws-iot-core-credential-provider-session-helper&amp;rdquo; a Python library to help simplify working with AWS IoT, &amp;ldquo;traffic-inspection-architectures-aws-cloud-wan&amp;rdquo; code that provides examples of different network architectures and how to do traffic inspection, &amp;ldquo;neptune-export&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you export your data in Amazon Neptune, &amp;ldquo;aws-organizations-tool&amp;rdquo; a command line tool to help you configure AWS Organisations, &amp;ldquo;sagemaker-external-repo-access&amp;rdquo; a nice reference architecture for Amazon Sagemaker, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-cfn-hook&amp;rdquo; a Python CDK app that will get you up and running quickly working with Cloudformation template hooks, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #144</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</guid>
      <description>Feb 5th, 2023 - Instalment #144 Welcome to edition #144 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. Some of the treats in store for you this week include &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-shell&amp;rdquo;, a project that provides a cli to your favourite AWS database, &amp;ldquo;precloud&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you catch issues with your configuration before you deploy, &amp;ldquo;node-latency-for-k8s&amp;rdquo; a tool to analyse your node logs, &amp;ldquo;stepfunctions-lambda-ec2-ssm&amp;rdquo; a very nice way of using step functions to overcome the 15 minute timeout of your lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;terraform-ec2-image-builder-container-hardening-pipeline&amp;rdquo; a very cool example of how to build an EC2 image hardening pipeline using Terraform, and &amp;ldquo;cloudtrail-event-fuzzy-viewer&amp;rdquo; a tool to copy your AWS CloudTrail events and then fuzzy search them on the command line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #129</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</guid>
      <description>September 30th, 2022 - Instalment #129 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #129.&#xA;We have loads of great new projects this week, with plenty of variety to keep you all interested. We have &amp;ldquo;aws-ecr-cleaner&amp;rdquo;, a great tool to help you manage your container images, &amp;ldquo;dotnet-lambda-sql-server-proxy&amp;rdquo; that shows you how you can use RDS Proxy with SQL Server and why, &amp;ldquo;minecraft-server-dashboard&amp;rdquo; perfect for those running their own minecraft servers, &amp;ldquo;YATAS&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;aws-security-survival-kit&amp;rdquo; for those working on security and governance, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-handler-cookbook&amp;rdquo; useful recipes to get you going, &amp;ldquo;autonomous-driving-data-framework&amp;rdquo; for folks working in the automotive space, and many more - make sure you check all the projects out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #115</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-115/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-115/</guid>
      <description>June 3rd, 2022 - Instalment #115 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #115.&#xA;This week we have another great selection of brand new open source projects for you to explore, including &amp;ldquo;firec&amp;rdquo; a Rust client library for interacting with Firecracker, &amp;ldquo;sfn-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool that helps you quickly build StepFunctions definitions, &amp;ldquo;ssm-cloner&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you replicate across AWS regions your AWS System Manager documents, &amp;ldquo;amazon-lambda-compute-tuning&amp;rdquo; an AWS Lambda function benchmarking tool, &amp;ldquo;aws-iam-root-user-activity-monitor&amp;rdquo; a sample project to help you keep track of your root user, &amp;ldquo;hpc-cost-simulator&amp;rdquo; a tool to help estimate costs running your HPC workloads on AWS, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
