<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CoreDNS on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/coredns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CoreDNS on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/coredns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #146</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</guid>
      <description>Feb 27th, 2023 - Instalment #146 Welcome to edition #146 of the AWS open source newsletter. This week we have another great selection of brand new, shiny open source projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. Some of the projects this week include &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-web-adapter&amp;rdquo; that will help you build portable Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;aws-marketplace-cli&amp;rdquo; if you want to escape the GUI when working with AWS Marketplace, this one is for you, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;otel-config-validator&amp;rdquo; helps you sanity check your configuration files, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-openai-chatbot-demo&amp;rdquo; build a personal assistance powered by ChatGPT, &amp;ldquo;drone-video-analysis&amp;rdquo; if you have wanted to use AI services to process your drone video footage, check this project out, &amp;ldquo;mask-words-in-image&amp;rdquo; a nice command line tool to quick mask data based on your needs, and many more cool projects.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
