<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataHub on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/datahub/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DataHub on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/datahub/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #143</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</guid>
      <description>January 30th, 2023 - Instalment #143 Welcome to edition #143 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. This week we feature projects including &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-in-electron&amp;rdquo;, a project that lets you put AWS CDK in a graphical user interface, &amp;ldquo;lightsail-k8s-installer&amp;rdquo; that helps you deploy Kubernetes into Amazon Lightsail, &amp;ldquo;porting-advisor-for-graviton&amp;rdquo; a great project to help you migrate to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, &amp;ldquo;aws-ebook-downloader&amp;rdquo; a browser tool to help you easily download pdf&amp;rsquo;s on AWS topics, &amp;ldquo;lake-formation-permissions-sync&amp;rdquo; a useful tool to help you keep on top of your Lake Formation setups, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #106</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-106/</guid>
      <description>March 28th, 2022 - Instalment #106 Newsletter #106.&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, and this week we have more great new open source projects to tell you about. We have &amp;ldquo;access-undenied-aws&amp;rdquo;, a tool that helps you better understand your CloudTrail logs and suggest remediation. &amp;ldquo;aws-slack-clickoops-watcher&amp;rdquo; provides you with a way to alert you when changes are made to your AWS environment. &amp;ldquo;kronicle&amp;rdquo; provides a way of illustrating your tech stack automagically, and we have many more tools, demos and sample projects to help get you started on a number of topics.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
