<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS ParallelCluster on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-parallelcluster/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS ParallelCluster on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-parallelcluster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #172</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</guid>
      <description>September 4th, 2023 - Instalment #172 Welcome to #172 of the AWS open source newsletter, your reliable source for all open source on AWS goodness. What do we have for you this week? Well, more new projects to check out, and plenty of fresh content on the open source projects you all love.&#xA;We have tools to help you export your DynamoDB tables as csv files, a tool that goes beyond tracking cost and actually shuts down resources to help you manage your AWS budget, a cool dashboard to help you stay on top of your EC2 configurations, a couple of useful utilities to simplify working with files on Amazon S3, and then a sample Cedar project that helps you implement a Lambda authoriser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #169</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</guid>
      <description>August 14th, 2023 - Instalment #169 Welcome to #169 of the AWS open source newsletter, featuring the latest and greatest open source news, projects, videos, and community content that you need to know about. Featured in this weeks edition we have more great projects, including a new ODBC driver for Amazon Timestream database, a nice tool to simplify your ssh tunnelling, an essential VSCode extension for working with Cedar policies, a couple of projects that help you shift left and validate / monitor your policies, a solution to help you monitor your Apache Kafka environments, as well as some great sample applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #164</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</guid>
      <description>July 10th, 2023 - Instalment #164 Welcome to #164 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;New projects this week will help you implement single table designs easily on Amazon DynamoDB, an experimental project to help you get to grips with Cedar, a comprehensive clickstream analytics project for your applications, web sites, and mobile applications, and some cool projects to help you with edge and hybrid use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #162</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-162/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-162/</guid>
      <description>June 26th, 2023 - Instalment #162 Welcome to #162 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;If you are looking for new projects to try out, then this weeks projects include a very handy tool for Amazon EKS admins, a new experimental project that looks to use ChatGPT to manage your AWS resources, a workshop on Generative AI on AWS, a new tool that helps simplify how you can connect to RDS resources, a PHP library to help you verify your JWT tokens, and a great example application of how you can use Cedar and Amazon Verified Permissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #158</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</guid>
      <description>May 30th, 2023 - Instalment #158 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #158. I hope some of you were able to catch the last episode of season two of Build on Open Source where we looked at some of the projects featured in this newsletter (specctl, eksdemo, and ec2-spot-placement-score-tracker). As always we pride ourself on this newsletter on giving you the newest, shiniest open source projects and this week we have some really great ones to share with you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #146</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</guid>
      <description>Feb 27th, 2023 - Instalment #146 Welcome to edition #146 of the AWS open source newsletter. This week we have another great selection of brand new, shiny open source projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. Some of the projects this week include &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-web-adapter&amp;rdquo; that will help you build portable Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;aws-marketplace-cli&amp;rdquo; if you want to escape the GUI when working with AWS Marketplace, this one is for you, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;otel-config-validator&amp;rdquo; helps you sanity check your configuration files, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-openai-chatbot-demo&amp;rdquo; build a personal assistance powered by ChatGPT, &amp;ldquo;drone-video-analysis&amp;rdquo; if you have wanted to use AI services to process your drone video footage, check this project out, &amp;ldquo;mask-words-in-image&amp;rdquo; a nice command line tool to quick mask data based on your needs, and many more cool projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #145</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-145/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-145/</guid>
      <description>Feb 20th, 2023 - Instalment #145 Welcome to edition #145 of the AWS open source newsletter. I hope some of you were able to catch the new Build on Open Source show we live streamed last Friday. You can catch up and replay the session by clicking on this link, where we went over a number of projects from this and a few previous newsletters, and we had special guest Valter who walked us through his project terraform-dev-containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #143</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</guid>
      <description>January 30th, 2023 - Instalment #143 Welcome to edition #143 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. This week we feature projects including &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-in-electron&amp;rdquo;, a project that lets you put AWS CDK in a graphical user interface, &amp;ldquo;lightsail-k8s-installer&amp;rdquo; that helps you deploy Kubernetes into Amazon Lightsail, &amp;ldquo;porting-advisor-for-graviton&amp;rdquo; a great project to help you migrate to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, &amp;ldquo;aws-ebook-downloader&amp;rdquo; a browser tool to help you easily download pdf&amp;rsquo;s on AWS topics, &amp;ldquo;lake-formation-permissions-sync&amp;rdquo; a useful tool to help you keep on top of your Lake Formation setups, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #140</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</guid>
      <description>January 9th, 2023 - Instalment #140 Welcome&#xA;Happy New Year and welcome to the first AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #140. If you have not already checked it out, I put together a short retrospective summary of 2022 in the post, AWS open source newsletter - 2022 in review. There are some interesting facts and figures in there. I am also taking time to collect feedback from readers to help shape where this newsletter goes in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #137</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-137/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-137/</guid>
      <description>November 25th, 2022 - Instalment #137 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #137. As it is re:Invent next week, I will be publishing the newsletter early as I am heading out on Monday. I will be in Las Vegas talking with open source Builders, hanging out on the Open Source Kiosk in the AWS Village, and doing some talks. If you are coming, I would love to meet some of you, so get in touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #134</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</guid>
      <description>November 7th, 2022 - Instalment #134 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #134. This weeks newsletter was featured in the latest Build on Open Source on twitch.tv/aws, so I hope some of you were able to tune in and watch.&#xA;New projects that we featured include &amp;ldquo;enclaver&amp;rdquo;, a toolkit to make working with enclaves easier, &amp;ldquo;s3crets_scanner&amp;rdquo; a new secrets scanning tool, &amp;ldquo;sandbox-accounts-for-events&amp;rdquo; a way to easily vend temporary environments, &amp;ldquo;frontend-discovery&amp;rdquo; helps you define and drive adoption of a frontend discovery patterns, &amp;ldquo;cf-sam-openapi-file-organization-demo&amp;rdquo;, a tool to help you get started with API development, &amp;ldquo;decoupling-microservices-lambda-amazonmq-rabbitmq&amp;rdquo; a sample solution to get you started on how to use micro services with RabbitMQ, &amp;ldquo;how-to-write-more-correct-software-workshop&amp;rdquo; a workshop to get you developing better software, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #127</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</guid>
      <description>September 16th, 2022 - Instalment #127 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #127. I hope some of you were able to catch Derek and myself sharing a peek at this edition, and enjoyed as our special guest, AWS Hero Ian Mckay walked us through some of his open source projects. It was very cool indeed, and if you have not yet watched, Ian shares an early glimpse of a new project - so make sure you check that out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #122</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-122/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-122/</guid>
      <description>July 29th, 2022 - Instalment #122 Welcome&#xA;Welcome back to my regular readers and hello to new readers, I hope you will enjoy and come back again to the AWS open source newsletter episode #122.&#xA;This week we have another great collection of community and AWS related open source tools, demos and samples for you to practice your open source four freedoms. &amp;ldquo;rds_auto_encrypt&amp;rdquo; helps you encrypt your Amazon RDS databases, &amp;ldquo;middy-profiler&amp;rdquo; is an interesting looking tool to help you understand performance characteristics of your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;simpleiot&amp;rdquo; is a very nice looking IoT framework to help simplify how you can onboard devices into AWS IoT, &amp;ldquo;aws-secrets-manager-hybrid-secret-replication-from-hashicorp-vault&amp;rdquo; (bit of a mouthful to say that one) helps you synchronise your secrets across different secret providers, &amp;ldquo;automated-forensic-orchestrator-for-amazon-ec2&amp;rdquo; is a very nice reference solution for automating some of your operational security activities, and we have several other projects for you to dive deep into.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #116</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-116/</guid>
      <description>June 10th, 2022 - Instalment #116 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #116.&#xA;Another selection of useful and interesting new open source projects for you to try out this week. First up, we have &amp;ldquo;aws-exec&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you do adhoc shell execution in AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;edgy&amp;rdquo; helps you simplify writing tests for Node.js based AWS CloudFront Lambda@Edge functions, &amp;ldquo;cdk-app-cli&amp;rdquo; a really nice cli that every AWS CDK user should know about, &amp;ldquo;Accumulus&amp;rdquo; a great looking reporting tool for AWS Lambda users, &amp;ldquo;sqldef-gitops-cdk&amp;rdquo; is a schema management for several open source databases, &amp;ldquo;log-hub&amp;rdquo; helps you to build your own log analytics tool using OpenSearch, &amp;ldquo;verifiable-controls-evidence-store&amp;rdquo; a very cool solution that builds a mechanism to centrally store findings and results of cloud security controls governing AWS workloads, and many more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #100</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-100/</guid>
      <description>Feb 14th, 2022 - Instalment #100 Newsletter #100.&#xA;Happy Valentines everyone, and welcome to this landmark 100st edition of this newsletter. This week we celebrate the love that many builders have for open source with more great new open source projects and content. Cuddle up to new projects that will help you build scalable systems, simplify your work with AWS DynamoDB, integrate your .NET applications with OpenSearch, keep on top of your VPC networks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #97</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-97/</guid>
      <description>Jan 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #97 Newsletter #97.&#xA;Welcome to another edition of the AWS open source newsletter, packed with more great new open source projects, content, and events. This week, we have new projects that help you improve security by de-obfuscating strings, a library to help you automate the configuration of your build pipelines, a new Terraform module, a nice new VSCode plugin that will help you when working with IAM, and several more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
