<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lambda Powertools on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/lambda-powertools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lambda Powertools on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/lambda-powertools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #98</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-98/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-98/</guid>
      <description>Jan 31st, 2022 - Instalment #98 Newsletter #98. Welcome to another edition of AWS open source news and updates, featuring more new open source projects. This week, these include eventbridge-assistant (a VScode plugin to help you whilst you are developing with Amazon EventBridge), stratus-red-team (a tool you can use to emulate offensive attack techniques), critter (AWS Config rule integration testing), syne-tune-s3-transfer (an example of how to apply the distributed parameter search library to optimise download performance), karpenter-terraform (a Terraform module to help you automate deployment of karpenter), and a couple of super interesting open source solutions covering last mile delivery and software defined radio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #96</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-96/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-96/</guid>
      <description>Jan 17th, 2022 - Instalment #96 Newsletter #96.&#xA;Welcome to another great round up of open source projects, news and great content. This week, we have new open source projects such as Event Catalog (that helps you to discover, explore and document your Event Driven Architectures), AWS Powertools for Lambda TypeScript edition, flowdog (an application/framework for inspection and manipulation of network traffic in AWS VPCs), ai-doorbell (a serverless AI enabled door bell) and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
