<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS Lambda Power Tools on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-lambda-power-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS Lambda Power Tools on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/aws-lambda-power-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #165</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-165/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-165/</guid>
      <description>July 17th, 2023 - Instalment #165 Welcome to #165 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only* newsletter that brings you the best and latest open source content. We have some great new projects this week, including a tool for IoT developers to help you validate your SQL statements, a command line interface tool for Amazon Verified Permissions, an Amazon DynamoDB estimation tool, and more. Also featured this week is content on Apache Iceberg, OpenSearch, PostgreSQL, Kubernetes, Power Tools for AWS Lambda, Spring Boot, Babelfish for Aurora PostgreSQL, Karpenter, Apollo GraphQL, JupyterHub, dbt, Apache Airflow, Cedar, and Apache Flink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #123</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</guid>
      <description>August, 5th, 2022 - Instalment #123 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter episode #123.&#xA;I sometimes speak with builders who are experienced developers but perhaps new to open source. A common question I get asked is what the impact of them working on open source might be on their careers. Whilst it is never a guarantee, open source can be a great career accelerator. I was reminded of that last week when reading the excellent post from Ran Isenberg, who shared his experience in his post How One Open-Source Code Donation Got Me Promoted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #121</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-121/</guid>
      <description>July 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #121 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #121.&#xA;Am super excited about this weeks new projects, including a number of AWS CDK related projects so if you are a fan of AWS CDK then make sure you check them all out. We feature projects such as &amp;ldquo;openrolesanywhere&amp;rdquo;, a proof of concept client for the recently released AWS IAM Roles Anywhere, &amp;ldquo;amazon-redshift-odbc-driver&amp;rdquo; an open source ODBC driver for Amazon Redshift, &amp;ldquo;spot-interruption-simulation&amp;rdquo; a very handy tool to help you test and simulate spot interuptions for your EC2 workloads, &amp;ldquo;magento-ecs-cdk&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy a scalable Magento environment, &amp;ldquo;using-rekognition-to-detect-sounds&amp;rdquo; a very interesting project that will help you hear sounds from your pictures (yes, you did not read that wrong!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
