<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>etcd on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/etcd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in etcd on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/etcd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #151</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-151/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-151/</guid>
      <description>April 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #151 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #151. This week sees more great new projects, including those covered in the latest episode of Build on Open Source, such as &amp;ldquo;ec2-former2&amp;rdquo; a way to host this great project to reverse engineer your CloudFormation templates, &amp;ldquo;protonizer&amp;rdquo; a cli tool for those using AWS Proton, &amp;ldquo;fortuna&amp;rdquo;, a library for Uncertainty Quantification, &amp;ldquo;aws-resilience-hub-tools&amp;rdquo; a set of tools and scripts for working with the AWS Resilience Hub, &amp;ldquo;jenkins-unity-build-on-aws&amp;rdquo; a nice reference solution for those needing to build Unity projects, &amp;ldquo;amazon-cognito-passwordless-auth&amp;rdquo; a nice demo of how to do authentication sans password, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
