<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Micronaut on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/micronaut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Micronaut on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/micronaut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #158</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</guid>
      <description>May 30th, 2023 - Instalment #158 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #158. I hope some of you were able to catch the last episode of season two of Build on Open Source where we looked at some of the projects featured in this newsletter (specctl, eksdemo, and ec2-spot-placement-score-tracker). As always we pride ourself on this newsletter on giving you the newest, shiniest open source projects and this week we have some really great ones to share with you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #139</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</guid>
      <description>December 18th, 2022 - Instalment #139 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the last AWS open source newsletter of 2022, edition #139. I am planning on take a few weeks off to recharge, and wish readers of this newsletter a fabulous Christmas and New Year. Over 100K of you have read this newsletter, so I want to thank you all for your continued support. This newsletter is only possible because of the passion and enthusiasm of open source Builders, and I look forward to seeing what 2023 will bring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #135</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-135/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-135/</guid>
      <description>November 11th, 2022 - Instalment #135 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #135.&#xA;What do we have in store for you in this weeks instalment? I am happy to report that we have yet more great new projects this week. These include &amp;ldquo;sovereign-keys&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;nitrogen&amp;rdquo; are new projects to help you secure and get started working with enclaves, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-scheduler&amp;rdquo; helps you schedule your events, &amp;ldquo;aws-resource-explorer-cli&amp;rdquo; provides a command line tool for this new capability, &amp;ldquo;workload-discovery-on-aws&amp;rdquo; helps you stay on top of your AWS workloads, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;image-content-moderation&amp;rdquo; provide a sample project for image moderation you can integrate into your workflows, &amp;ldquo;cloudenv&amp;rdquo; is a proof of concept that explores managing secrets and prameters, &amp;ldquo;cdk-schema-watcher&amp;rdquo; is a tool to help you stay notified of schema changes in your event driven applications, and several other projects to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #100</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-100/</guid>
      <description>Feb 14th, 2022 - Instalment #100 Newsletter #100.&#xA;Happy Valentines everyone, and welcome to this landmark 100st edition of this newsletter. This week we celebrate the love that many builders have for open source with more great new open source projects and content. Cuddle up to new projects that will help you build scalable systems, simplify your work with AWS DynamoDB, integrate your .NET applications with OpenSearch, keep on top of your VPC networks, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
