<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsletters on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsletters on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #182</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-182/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-182/</guid>
      <description>December 11th, 2023 - Instalment #182 Welcome to #182 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This is a special re:Invent packed edition of this newsletter, attempting to catch up and cover all the main talking points, sessions, and announcements. Whilst there is a lot of content to go through, I know that many of you will still be wanting to know about new projects you can try out, and the good news is that we have plenty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #181</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-181/</guid>
      <description>November 27th, 2023 - Instalment #181 Welcome to #181 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As some of you will know, this is re:Invent week, where many of my colleagues and tens of thousands of developers will be congregating to learn about Cloud, and hopefully discover plenty of open source goodness too. If you are going, make sure to visit the open source booth in the Expo floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #180</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-180/</guid>
      <description>November 20th, 2023 - Instalment #180 Welcome to #180 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. As we ramp up to re:Invent, it is good to see that pre:Invent is giving us plenty of open source goodies. In this weeks newsletter, we have some of those in the way of new projects such as res and aws-iatk, but we also have lots of really great content too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #179</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-179/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-179/</guid>
      <description>November 13th, 2023 - Instalment #179 Welcome to #179 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This weeks new projects include an open source tool that provides similar capabilities to AWS Control Tower, a tool for enrolling your Mac based EC2 instances into mobile device management (MDM) solution, a very neat tool to help you compare costs of running your CodePipeline jobs, as well as sample code that shows you how you can use Karpenter to optimise IP address use, examples of using Test Containers with AWS CDK, generative AI technologies such as LangChain, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #178</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-178/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-178/</guid>
      <description>November 6th, 2023 - Instalment #178 Welcome to #178 of the AWS open source newsletter, the place for all your AWS and open source needs. This week we feature more new open source projects for you to practice your four freedoms. We have a useful tool that helps you synchronise your AWS Identity Centre users with the users you provision in your Amazon RDS databases, we share the AWS data solutions framework that helps you build data solutions following opinionated best practices, a resource explorer for your AWS accounts, a guardrails solution for your AWS account, and a couple of demo repositories that take a look at Localstack and RSS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #177</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-177/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-177/</guid>
      <description>October 30th, 2023 - Instalment #177 Welcome to #177 of the AWS open source newsletter, the Halloween special. You will find no tricks in this edition, only treats, with more new projects for you to check out and content that are a feast for your eyes. This weeks new projects include a tool to help you easily deploy vector databases on Kubernetes, an observability toolkit, a tool to help you benchmark network latency, as well as lots of new demos on generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #176</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-176/</guid>
      <description>October 23rd, 2023 - Instalment #176 Welcome to #176 of the AWS open source newsletter, heading into Autumn and getting ready for the clocks to go back later in the week. How will you use that extra hour? Well, perhaps some of you might use it to check out this weeks new projects, which include a nice cli chat tool that uses Amazon Bedrock, a tool to help simplify deploying VSCode in the Cloud environments, and sample demos and code on chaos engineering, deploying Amazon Bedrock via AWS Lambda, and how you can use IAM Roles Anywhere to authenticate against external identity providers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #175</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-175/</guid>
      <description>October 16th, 2023 - Instalment #175 Welcome to #175 of the AWS open source newsletter, back after recharging in the wonderful countyside of Yorkshire. I am publishing this weeks newsletter from Raleigh, North Carolina. All Things Open is happening this week, and you will catch me at the AWS booth where I will be showing off some cool open source stuff (Cedar, Apache Airflow, and a few others), and I also have a talk on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #174</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-174/</guid>
      <description>September 18th, 2023 - Instalment #174 Welcome to #174 of the AWS open source newsletter, which will be the last one for a couple of weeks as I take some time off to recharge. I will be back in early October with more open source goodness, but in the meantime, you still have this edition packed with open source goodness.&#xA;This weeks new projects include a Rust tool to help you keep your CloudFormation stacks up to date, a tool to help upload files to Amazon S3, a generative AI tool that aims to help you review and detect IAM configuration issues, an updated JDBC driver for connecting to Amazon Aurora, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #173</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-173/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-173/</guid>
      <description>September 11th, 2023 - Instalment #173 Welcome to #173 of the AWS open source newsletter, bringing you all the news and latest projects for AWS developers. This weeks new projects include a Golang based SDK for kernel eBPF operations, a project that helps you to optimise your network performance, a couple of projects for Apache Flink users, as well as a handful of different tools and demos featuring open source technologies helping to drive innovation in generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #172</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-172/</guid>
      <description>September 4th, 2023 - Instalment #172 Welcome to #172 of the AWS open source newsletter, your reliable source for all open source on AWS goodness. What do we have for you this week? Well, more new projects to check out, and plenty of fresh content on the open source projects you all love.&#xA;We have tools to help you export your DynamoDB tables as csv files, a tool that goes beyond tracking cost and actually shuts down resources to help you manage your AWS budget, a cool dashboard to help you stay on top of your EC2 configurations, a couple of useful utilities to simplify working with files on Amazon S3, and then a sample Cedar project that helps you implement a Lambda authoriser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #171</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-171/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-171/</guid>
      <description>August 29th, 2023 - Instalment #171 Welcome to #171 of the AWS open source newsletter, the newsletter created for developers passionate about open source. Thanks to the wonderful August bank holiday here in the UK, we are publishing a day later than usual. If you have not read this newsletter before, we feature new projects, content from across the open source and AWS community, and share events and videos that you should check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #170</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-170/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-170/</guid>
      <description>August 21st, 2023 - Instalment #170 Welcome to edition #170 of the AWS open source newsletter, an oasis of open source goodness that features the latest new projects, essential reading, and must view videos to quench the thirst of every open source developer. This weeks edition we have new projects that help you get on top of your IAM actions, a handy tool for knowing what your current AWS account service limits are from the command line, a tool to help you do database migrations, and some interesting and very detailed reference solutions for gaming, live streaming, and managing/exporting of your Amazon Cognito profiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #169</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</guid>
      <description>August 14th, 2023 - Instalment #169 Welcome to #169 of the AWS open source newsletter, featuring the latest and greatest open source news, projects, videos, and community content that you need to know about. Featured in this weeks edition we have more great projects, including a new ODBC driver for Amazon Timestream database, a nice tool to simplify your ssh tunnelling, an essential VSCode extension for working with Cedar policies, a couple of projects that help you shift left and validate / monitor your policies, a solution to help you monitor your Apache Kafka environments, as well as some great sample applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #168</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-168/</guid>
      <description>August 7th, 2023 - Instalment #168 Welcome to #168 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only newsletter that features the freshest open source and AWS content*&#xA;New projects for you to feast on in this issue include the obligatory projects that look at how Generative AI can help developers be more productive, in this case by making documentation more relevant and easier to find and to help with code reviews, a nice tool to help you query your AWS Identity Access Management (IAM) policies, and a security focused tool to help you search for potentially incorrect configured S3 buckets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #167</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-167/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-167/</guid>
      <description>July 31st, 2023 - Instalment #167 Welcome to #167 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another edition packed with new open source projects for you to explore. Whether you are new to this newsletter, or returning (we thank you!) there is something for you. This week we have projects that will help use Terraform to deploy your monolith applications, a tool to accelerate your GraphQL building when working with Amazon DynamoDB, a project that will help you introduce chaos without changes to your code, and a couple of really nice demos of using generative AI that allows you to use natural language to query your data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #166</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-166/</guid>
      <description>July 24th, 2023 - Instalment #166 Welcome to #166 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;This weeks new projects include a library to help you managed and validate your environment variables when working with AWS Lambda, a new Rust based tool for interacting with your S3 buckets, an essential tool to help CDK developers remove a lot of the setup work, and a tool that helps you run Yocto embedded Linux build jobs in AWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #165</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-165/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-165/</guid>
      <description>July 17th, 2023 - Instalment #165 Welcome to #165 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only* newsletter that brings you the best and latest open source content. We have some great new projects this week, including a tool for IoT developers to help you validate your SQL statements, a command line interface tool for Amazon Verified Permissions, an Amazon DynamoDB estimation tool, and more. Also featured this week is content on Apache Iceberg, OpenSearch, PostgreSQL, Kubernetes, Power Tools for AWS Lambda, Spring Boot, Babelfish for Aurora PostgreSQL, Karpenter, Apollo GraphQL, JupyterHub, dbt, Apache Airflow, Cedar, and Apache Flink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #164</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-164/</guid>
      <description>July 10th, 2023 - Instalment #164 Welcome to #164 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;New projects this week will help you implement single table designs easily on Amazon DynamoDB, an experimental project to help you get to grips with Cedar, a comprehensive clickstream analytics project for your applications, web sites, and mobile applications, and some cool projects to help you with edge and hybrid use cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #163</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-163/</guid>
      <description>July 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #163 Welcome to #163 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week. This weeks featured projects include a Cedar authorisation service and demo examples, a tool to help you find dangling DNS records, a new CLI for those using Amazon ECR, an accelerator for observability on AWS, a serverless web analytics solution (so good, that I implemented it myself), and several more projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #162</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-162/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-162/</guid>
      <description>June 26th, 2023 - Instalment #162 Welcome to #162 of the AWS open source newsletter. As always, we search high and low for the best and latest open source content, and I think you will love what we have lined up this week.&#xA;If you are looking for new projects to try out, then this weeks projects include a very handy tool for Amazon EKS admins, a new experimental project that looks to use ChatGPT to manage your AWS resources, a workshop on Generative AI on AWS, a new tool that helps simplify how you can connect to RDS resources, a PHP library to help you verify your JWT tokens, and a great example application of how you can use Cedar and Amazon Verified Permissions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #161</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-161/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-161/</guid>
      <description>June 19th, 2023 - Instalment #161 Welcome to #161 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week for fresh, new open source projects and code for you to practice your four freedoms. This weeks projects include tools that will help you create temporary elevated credentials, a new Java library that provides methods for encrypting and decrypting cryptographic materials, an AWS DynamoDB wrapper for Node/TypeScript developers, and a solution to help you find and visualise data assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #160</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-160/</guid>
      <description>June 12th, 2023 - Instalment #160 Welcome to #160 of the AWS open source newsletter, where we try and share all the important open source news, projects, events, and content that open source builders want. This week we have new projects that include tools to help you build data workflows, Terraform modules to help you incorporate temporary elevated access controls, integrating Tailscale to change your traffic flows, a neat AWS Lambda debugging tool, Go bindings for Cedar, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #159</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-159/</guid>
      <description>June 5th, 2023 - Instalment #159 Welcome to #159 of the AWS open source newsletter, where we try and share all the important open source news, projects, events, and content that open source builders want. This week we have new projects that include tools to help you generate test data, an accelerator for stable diffusion, tools to help you with managing application credentials and variables, a new connector for Apache Kafka, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #158</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-158/</guid>
      <description>May 30th, 2023 - Instalment #158 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #158. I hope some of you were able to catch the last episode of season two of Build on Open Source where we looked at some of the projects featured in this newsletter (specctl, eksdemo, and ec2-spot-placement-score-tracker). As always we pride ourself on this newsletter on giving you the newest, shiniest open source projects and this week we have some really great ones to share with you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #157</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-157/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-157/</guid>
      <description>May 22nd, 2023 - Instalment #157 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #157. Apologies for the lack of newsletter last week, but hopefully this week will make up for that as we have a bumper selection of great open source content for you. This weeks new projects include repos that help you get OpenEMR up and running (&amp;ldquo;host-openemr-on-aws-fargate&amp;rdquo;), two new security related open source projects that you definitely need to check out, (&amp;ldquo;cedar&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;snapchange&amp;rdquo;), integration of clickstream analytics using Swift (&amp;ldquo;clickstream-swift&amp;rdquo;), deployment of Backstage to serve up access to your AWS resources, (&amp;ldquo;app-development-for-backstage-io-on-aws&amp;rdquo;), a tool to help you clean up ecs tasks definitions (&amp;ldquo;aws-ecs-task-definition-cleanup&amp;rdquo;) and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #156</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-156/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-156/</guid>
      <description>May 8th, 2023 - Instalment #156 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #156, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. So what do we have for you this week? Coming up later in this newsletter we have projects such as &amp;ldquo;sustainability-scanner&amp;rdquo; helps you check your Cloudformation templates against sustainability good practices, &amp;ldquo;synthtable&amp;rdquo; helps you create synthetic data for different use cases, &amp;ldquo;neptune-gremlin-client&amp;rdquo; a Java based Gremlin client, &amp;ldquo;s3zipper&amp;rdquo; a tool to quickly download entire S3 buckets, &amp;ldquo;chataws&amp;rdquo; a nice demo of how you can use ChatGPT to aid your AWS deployments, and plenty of other great projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #155</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-155/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-155/</guid>
      <description>May 1st, 2023 - Instalment #155 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #155, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. This week&amp;rsquo;s new projects include&#xA;&amp;ldquo;aws-cloudformation-controller-for-flux&amp;rdquo; provides a way to use flux to orchestrate your CloudFormation deployments, &amp;ldquo;threat-composer&amp;rdquo; is a nice React based tool to help you create Threat Models for your systems and applications, &amp;ldquo;cdk-integ-tests-sample&amp;rdquo; a tool to allow you to do integration tests with your CDK stacks (these three were all featured in the latest episode of Build on Open Source, you can watch it here), &amp;ldquo;iam-access-key-report&amp;rdquo; generates reports from your AWS accounts about your AWS access keys, &amp;ldquo;personalize-kafka-connector&amp;rdquo; provides an integration into Apache Kafka for this AWS service, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #154</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-154/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-154/</guid>
      <description>April 24th, 2023 - Instalment #154 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #154, the newsletter that just keeps on giving&amp;hellip;.in this case, keeps giving you brand new open source projects to practice your four freedoms on. We have another great selection of projects for you as always, starting off with &amp;ldquo;cfn-teleport&amp;rdquo; an essential cli tool for Cloudformation users, &amp;ldquo;aither&amp;rdquo; an interesting collaborative development tool using virtualised desktops on containers, &amp;ldquo;tabular-column-semantic-search&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you find similar types of data in your data lakes, &amp;ldquo;resource-lister&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;komiser&amp;rdquo; tools that help you manage your AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;resource-utilization&amp;rdquo; helps you track your AWS resource utilisation, &amp;ldquo;iot-network-traffic-control-and-load-testing-simulator&amp;rdquo; an interesting load and chaos testing example, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #153</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-153/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-153/</guid>
      <description>April 17th, 2023 - Instalment #153 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #153 as featured in the latest episode of Build on Open Source (S2E5) . We have lots of great projects for you this week, with a strong chatGPT influence. &amp;ldquo;pg_gpt&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;cw-logs-insights-gpt&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;aiws&amp;rdquo; all integrate chatGPT to help you do different things on AWS, &amp;ldquo;semantic-search-aws-docs&amp;rdquo; is a very interesting demo on how to build a more coherent search for your documentation, &amp;ldquo;aws-chime-chat-demo&amp;rdquo; a very nice demo using the Chime SDK, &amp;ldquo;ckia&amp;rdquo; is an open source AWS Trusted Advisor tool, &amp;ldquo;AWS_ED&amp;rdquo; helps you keep your local IP in sync with external DNS records, &amp;ldquo;cfnctl&amp;rdquo; provides a Terraform like cli experience to CloudFormation, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #152</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-152/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-152/</guid>
      <description>April 10th, 2023 - Instalment #152 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #152 an Easter special. This week sees more great new projects including, &amp;ldquo;redshift-test-drive&amp;rdquo; a set of essential tools for Amazon Redshift users, &amp;ldquo;simple-database-archival-solution&amp;rdquo; a nice tool to help you archive your data, &amp;ldquo;attribution-gen&amp;rdquo; a Go tool to help you build open source attribution documents, &amp;ldquo;aws-glue-data-catalog-federation&amp;rdquo; a library to help you federate your Glue catalog, &amp;ldquo;subnet-utilization-monitor-for-amazon-vpc&amp;rdquo; a handy tool to keep on top of your IP address allocation, &amp;ldquo;AlexaGPT&amp;rdquo; a demo of integrating Alexa with you know what, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #151</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-151/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-151/</guid>
      <description>April 3rd, 2023 - Instalment #151 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, #151. This week sees more great new projects, including those covered in the latest episode of Build on Open Source, such as &amp;ldquo;ec2-former2&amp;rdquo; a way to host this great project to reverse engineer your CloudFormation templates, &amp;ldquo;protonizer&amp;rdquo; a cli tool for those using AWS Proton, &amp;ldquo;fortuna&amp;rdquo;, a library for Uncertainty Quantification, &amp;ldquo;aws-resilience-hub-tools&amp;rdquo; a set of tools and scripts for working with the AWS Resilience Hub, &amp;ldquo;jenkins-unity-build-on-aws&amp;rdquo; a nice reference solution for those needing to build Unity projects, &amp;ldquo;amazon-cognito-passwordless-auth&amp;rdquo; a nice demo of how to do authentication sans password, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #150</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-150/</guid>
      <description>March 27th, 2023 - Instalment #150 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to a milestone edition of the AWS open source newsletter, #150. Over two hundred thousand words later, thousands of contributors, hundreds of new open source projects, I hope this newsletter brings as much joy for readers as it does for me to put this together. Thank you all for your amazing support so far. What do we have in store for you this week?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #149</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-149/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-149/</guid>
      <description>March 20th, 2023 - Instalment #149 Welcome&#xA;Hello and welcome to edition #149 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only newsletter on the planet that serves you up a weekly dose of the freshest, latest open source projects on AWS. I hope some of you were able to catch this episode reviewed on our last Build on Open Source livestream. If not, you can catch the replay here. This week we have projects such &amp;ldquo;mountpoint-s3&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;s3-access-for-squash&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;amazon-s3-tar-tool&amp;rdquo; which provide some useful tools for managing your files on S3, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-ai-stories&amp;rdquo; a creative masterclass in storytelling, &amp;ldquo;earthquake-notifier&amp;rdquo; a serverless solution to keep you alerted and ready, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #148</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-148/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-148/</guid>
      <description>March 13th, 2023 - Instalment #148 Welcome&#xA;Hello and a warm welcome to edition #148 of the AWS open source newsletter, the only newsletter on the planet that serves you up a weekly dose of the freshest, latest open source projects on AWS. This week we have projects such as &amp;ldquo;iam-ape&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you grapple with your IAM policies, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-cli&amp;rdquo; a nice command line tool to package and deploy your Spark jobs on Amazon EMR, &amp;ldquo;duckdb-athena-extension&amp;rdquo; that helps you import data from Amazon Athena into DuckDB, &amp;ldquo;terraform-aws-email-files-dropped-in-s3&amp;rdquo; a helpful tool to easily email you attachments automatically, &amp;ldquo;cloud-queue-for-quantum-devices&amp;rdquo; a tool to help Quantum researchers across the world, &amp;ldquo;aws-private-ca-matter-infrastructure&amp;rdquo; a sample reference architecture for setting up a secure, private certificate authority, &amp;ldquo;aws-sam-cli-java-examples&amp;rdquo; will help you deploy your Java apps via AWS SAM, &amp;ldquo;mpartman&amp;rdquo; a PostgreSQL partition manager, &amp;ldquo;aws-do-pcluster&amp;rdquo; simplifying how to run AWS ParallelCluster, &amp;ldquo;staticwebsite-cli&amp;rdquo; a very nice too to help you easily deploy static web sites, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #147</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-147/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-147/</guid>
      <description>March 6th, 2023 - Instalment #147 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to edition #147 of the AWS open source newsletter, featured in the latest episode of Build on Open Source. This week we have new projects such as &amp;ldquo;metahub&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;savings-estimator&amp;rdquo; that we looked at in closer detail on the Build on Open Source livestream, &amp;ldquo;aws-iot-core-credential-provider-session-helper&amp;rdquo; a Python library to help simplify working with AWS IoT, &amp;ldquo;traffic-inspection-architectures-aws-cloud-wan&amp;rdquo; code that provides examples of different network architectures and how to do traffic inspection, &amp;ldquo;neptune-export&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you export your data in Amazon Neptune, &amp;ldquo;aws-organizations-tool&amp;rdquo; a command line tool to help you configure AWS Organisations, &amp;ldquo;sagemaker-external-repo-access&amp;rdquo; a nice reference architecture for Amazon Sagemaker, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-cfn-hook&amp;rdquo; a Python CDK app that will get you up and running quickly working with Cloudformation template hooks, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #146</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-146/</guid>
      <description>Feb 27th, 2023 - Instalment #146 Welcome to edition #146 of the AWS open source newsletter. This week we have another great selection of brand new, shiny open source projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. Some of the projects this week include &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-web-adapter&amp;rdquo; that will help you build portable Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;aws-marketplace-cli&amp;rdquo; if you want to escape the GUI when working with AWS Marketplace, this one is for you, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;otel-config-validator&amp;rdquo; helps you sanity check your configuration files, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-openai-chatbot-demo&amp;rdquo; build a personal assistance powered by ChatGPT, &amp;ldquo;drone-video-analysis&amp;rdquo; if you have wanted to use AI services to process your drone video footage, check this project out, &amp;ldquo;mask-words-in-image&amp;rdquo; a nice command line tool to quick mask data based on your needs, and many more cool projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #145</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-145/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-145/</guid>
      <description>Feb 20th, 2023 - Instalment #145 Welcome to edition #145 of the AWS open source newsletter. I hope some of you were able to catch the new Build on Open Source show we live streamed last Friday. You can catch up and replay the session by clicking on this link, where we went over a number of projects from this and a few previous newsletters, and we had special guest Valter who walked us through his project terraform-dev-containers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #144</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-144/</guid>
      <description>Feb 5th, 2023 - Instalment #144 Welcome to edition #144 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. Some of the treats in store for you this week include &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-shell&amp;rdquo;, a project that provides a cli to your favourite AWS database, &amp;ldquo;precloud&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you catch issues with your configuration before you deploy, &amp;ldquo;node-latency-for-k8s&amp;rdquo; a tool to analyse your node logs, &amp;ldquo;stepfunctions-lambda-ec2-ssm&amp;rdquo; a very nice way of using step functions to overcome the 15 minute timeout of your lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;terraform-ec2-image-builder-container-hardening-pipeline&amp;rdquo; a very cool example of how to build an EC2 image hardening pipeline using Terraform, and &amp;ldquo;cloudtrail-event-fuzzy-viewer&amp;rdquo; a tool to copy your AWS CloudTrail events and then fuzzy search them on the command line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #143</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</guid>
      <description>January 30th, 2023 - Instalment #143 Welcome to edition #143 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. This week we feature projects including &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-in-electron&amp;rdquo;, a project that lets you put AWS CDK in a graphical user interface, &amp;ldquo;lightsail-k8s-installer&amp;rdquo; that helps you deploy Kubernetes into Amazon Lightsail, &amp;ldquo;porting-advisor-for-graviton&amp;rdquo; a great project to help you migrate to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, &amp;ldquo;aws-ebook-downloader&amp;rdquo; a browser tool to help you easily download pdf&amp;rsquo;s on AWS topics, &amp;ldquo;lake-formation-permissions-sync&amp;rdquo; a useful tool to help you keep on top of your Lake Formation setups, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #142</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-142/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-142/</guid>
      <description>January 23rd, 2023 - Instalment #142 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to edition #142 of the AWS open source newsletter.&#xA;We have another great round up of new projects for you to get stuck into. Here are just a taste of some of the projects, kicking off with &amp;ldquo;sls-mentor&amp;rdquo; a new tool to help you assess your serverless applications, &amp;ldquo;subnet-watcher&amp;rdquo;, a tool to help you monitor your IP addresses, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-web-administered-apps&amp;rdquo; a very nice reference solution for applications that have a user and admin component, &amp;ldquo;serverless-newsletter-app&amp;rdquo; if you are looking for a newsletter solution and want to host your own, look here first, &amp;ldquo;aws-iot-with-privatelink&amp;rdquo; shows you how you use private networks for your IoT traffic, &amp;ldquo;emr-spark-benchmark&amp;rdquo; benchmarking tool for assessing your Amazon EMR environments, and &amp;ldquo;update-aws-ip-ranges&amp;rdquo; keep automatically updated on Amazon&amp;rsquo;s IP address ranges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #141</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</guid>
      <description>January 16th, 2023 - Instalment #141 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #141.&#xA;This week we have more new projects for you to practice your four freedoms, including &amp;ldquo;distributed-compute-on-aws-with-cross-regional-dask&amp;rdquo;, a solution to simplify distributed compute using Dask, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-serverless-image-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool to verify your Amazon EMR custom container images, &amp;ldquo;serverless-run-watch&amp;rdquo; a tool to help accelerate your local development if you are using the Serverless Framework, &amp;ldquo;aws-sso-auto-expand-accounts&amp;rdquo; a quick browser extension for those using AWS SSO, &amp;ldquo;basti&amp;rdquo; a cool Bastion Host alternative, &amp;ldquo;klotho&amp;rdquo; generate cloud native code from your code, &amp;ldquo;amazon-route53-hosted-zone-sync&amp;rdquo; a nice solution for hybrid DNS use cases, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #140</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-140/</guid>
      <description>January 9th, 2023 - Instalment #140 Welcome&#xA;Happy New Year and welcome to the first AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #140. If you have not already checked it out, I put together a short retrospective summary of 2022 in the post, AWS open source newsletter - 2022 in review. There are some interesting facts and figures in there. I am also taking time to collect feedback from readers to help shape where this newsletter goes in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter - 2022 in review</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-newsletter-2022-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-newsletter-2022-review/</guid>
      <description>The AWS open source newsletter - review of 2022&#xA;I wanted to kick off 2023 by sharing some data points and things of interest that came up in 2022 as part of writing and putting together this open source newsletter. Given the nature of the newsletter, and that transparency and openness is core to open source, I hope these might be interesting to some of you.&#xA;In 2022, I published 45 newsletters over the course of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #139</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-139/</guid>
      <description>December 18th, 2022 - Instalment #139 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the last AWS open source newsletter of 2022, edition #139. I am planning on take a few weeks off to recharge, and wish readers of this newsletter a fabulous Christmas and New Year. Over 100K of you have read this newsletter, so I want to thank you all for your continued support. This newsletter is only possible because of the passion and enthusiasm of open source Builders, and I look forward to seeing what 2023 will bring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #138</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</guid>
      <description>December 12th, 2022 - Instalment #138 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #138. After a week off due to re:Invent, this edition is packed with content on many of the open source related announcements. As always, we have a great line up of new projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. In no particular order, we have projects like &amp;ldquo;eks-node-viewer&amp;rdquo;, a nice visualisation tool for your Amazon EKS clusters, &amp;ldquo;pg_tle&amp;rdquo; a great new project to make your PostgreSQL environments safer, &amp;ldquo;dyna53&amp;rdquo; a fun project that finally turns Amazon Route 53 into a database, &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-mass-migrations&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you migrate to Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;visual-asset-management-system&amp;rdquo; a very nice digital asset management tool, &amp;ldquo;fast-differential-privacy&amp;rdquo; implement differential privacy in your PyTorch models, &amp;ldquo;migration-hadoop-to-emr-tco-simulator&amp;rdquo; a handy total cost of ownership calculator for Amazon EMR, &amp;ldquo;realtime-toxicity-detection&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you stay on top of your online communities, &amp;ldquo;functionclarity&amp;rdquo; a very cool tool to check the integrity of your serverless functions before executing, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #137</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-137/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-137/</guid>
      <description>November 25th, 2022 - Instalment #137 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #137. As it is re:Invent next week, I will be publishing the newsletter early as I am heading out on Monday. I will be in Las Vegas talking with open source Builders, hanging out on the Open Source Kiosk in the AWS Village, and doing some talks. If you are coming, I would love to meet some of you, so get in touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #136</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-136/</guid>
      <description>November 21st, 2022 - Instalment #136 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #136, as featured on the latest episode of Build on Open Source. This week we feature new projects including &amp;ldquo;dynamoit&amp;rdquo; a JavaFX gui for Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;building-apache-kafka-connectors&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;msk-config-providers&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;msk-serverless-data-pipeline&amp;rdquo; projects to help make your life easier when working with Apache Kafka, &amp;ldquo;stowrs-to-s3&amp;rdquo; a tool for working with STOWRS data on AWS, &amp;ldquo;aws-device-lobby&amp;rdquo; a tool to make onboarding devices into AWS IoT Core easier, &amp;ldquo;aws-graviton-run-confidential-ml-workloads-using-nitro-enclaves&amp;rdquo; a nice example of how you can do Confidential Computing for machine learning use cases, &amp;ldquo;aws-hpc-builder&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you manage your open source HPC tools, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #135</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-135/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-135/</guid>
      <description>November 11th, 2022 - Instalment #135 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #135.&#xA;What do we have in store for you in this weeks instalment? I am happy to report that we have yet more great new projects this week. These include &amp;ldquo;sovereign-keys&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;nitrogen&amp;rdquo; are new projects to help you secure and get started working with enclaves, &amp;ldquo;aws-serverless-scheduler&amp;rdquo; helps you schedule your events, &amp;ldquo;aws-resource-explorer-cli&amp;rdquo; provides a command line tool for this new capability, &amp;ldquo;workload-discovery-on-aws&amp;rdquo; helps you stay on top of your AWS workloads, &amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;image-content-moderation&amp;rdquo; provide a sample project for image moderation you can integrate into your workflows, &amp;ldquo;cloudenv&amp;rdquo; is a proof of concept that explores managing secrets and prameters, &amp;ldquo;cdk-schema-watcher&amp;rdquo; is a tool to help you stay notified of schema changes in your event driven applications, and several other projects to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #134</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</guid>
      <description>November 7th, 2022 - Instalment #134 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #134. This weeks newsletter was featured in the latest Build on Open Source on twitch.tv/aws, so I hope some of you were able to tune in and watch.&#xA;New projects that we featured include &amp;ldquo;enclaver&amp;rdquo;, a toolkit to make working with enclaves easier, &amp;ldquo;s3crets_scanner&amp;rdquo; a new secrets scanning tool, &amp;ldquo;sandbox-accounts-for-events&amp;rdquo; a way to easily vend temporary environments, &amp;ldquo;frontend-discovery&amp;rdquo; helps you define and drive adoption of a frontend discovery patterns, &amp;ldquo;cf-sam-openapi-file-organization-demo&amp;rdquo;, a tool to help you get started with API development, &amp;ldquo;decoupling-microservices-lambda-amazonmq-rabbitmq&amp;rdquo; a sample solution to get you started on how to use micro services with RabbitMQ, &amp;ldquo;how-to-write-more-correct-software-workshop&amp;rdquo; a workshop to get you developing better software, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #133</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-133/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-133/</guid>
      <description>October 28th, 2022 - Instalment #133 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #133. This week has been all about KubeCon, and there were some important announcements from AWS. If you missed these, I have tried to capture the important ones here, but I want to start off with probably my favourite which was the announcement during Nate Taber keynote on some of the investments we are providing to CNCF and OpenSSF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #132</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</guid>
      <description>October 21st, 2022 - Instalment #132 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #132. This newsletter was covered in last Friday&amp;rsquo;s Build on Open Source, so if you missed it, don&amp;rsquo;t worry as you can view episode five of Build on Open Source. In this episode special guest Abhishek Gupta walked us through how to use cdk8s using Golang, building a Wordpress site in minutes.&#xA;New projects this week include &amp;ldquo;duvet&amp;rdquo; a tool to help honour RFC in code, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-explorer&amp;rdquo; a gui tool to explore your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;k3s-aws-terraform-cluster&amp;rdquo; deploy k3s on AWS via Terraform, &amp;ldquo;snow-transfer-tool&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you transfer data via Snowball devices, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-vscode-toolkit&amp;rdquo; a new VSCode plugin for Amazon EMR users, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-for-discourse&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy the open source discourse tool, &amp;ldquo;image-optimization&amp;rdquo; a reference example of how to do image optimising, and &amp;ldquo;gtfs-serverless-ticketing-sample&amp;rdquo; a sample application using public transport data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #131</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-131/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-131/</guid>
      <description>October 17th, 2022 - Instalment #131 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #131. This week&amp;rsquo;s new projects include &amp;ldquo;metahub&amp;rdquo;, a command line way to interact with AWS Security Hub, &amp;ldquo;somod&amp;rdquo; a framework for creating micro applications in serverless, &amp;ldquo;terraform-aws-guardduty-multiaccount&amp;rdquo; a Terraform module to help you automate your AWS Guard Duty configuration, &amp;ldquo;aws-glue-cdk-cicd&amp;rdquo; a sample project to automate the creation data pipelines using AWS Glue, &amp;ldquo;go-kafka-event-source&amp;rdquo; an Apache Kafka client in Go, &amp;ldquo;project-tools&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you get insights from your GitHub repo, &amp;ldquo;eks-event-watcher&amp;rdquo; a command line tool to tail your Amazon EKS logs, &amp;ldquo;listmonk-based-edm-solution&amp;rdquo; an example of how to deploy this open source mailing list tool, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #130</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-130/</guid>
      <description>October 10th, 2022 - Instalment #130 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #130. This newsletter was featured in the Build on Open Source episode four, which you can check out here if you missed it.&#xA;New projects for you to practice your open source four freedoms this week include &amp;ldquo;grucloud&amp;rdquo; a new infrastructure as code tool with some nice features, &amp;ldquo;stepfunctions-sdk-autocomplete&amp;rdquo; a VSCode plugin for all you AWS Step Functions fans, &amp;ldquo;AWS_Billing_Overage_Shutdown&amp;rdquo; a very new repo that has some code to help you automate shutting down resources on alerts, &amp;ldquo;aws-secrets-manager-github-action&amp;rdquo; if you are using GitHub Actions, this one is for you, &amp;ldquo;meta-aws&amp;rdquo;, tools and recipes for those using and building with Yocto, &amp;ldquo;data-on-eks&amp;rdquo; a number of sample solutions to configure self managed open source data analytics tools, &amp;ldquo;cql-replicator&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you migrate from self managed Apache Cassandra to Amazon Keyspaces, &amp;ldquo;ec2-imagebuilder-ami-lifecycle&amp;rdquo; provides some new capabilities for those building AMIs, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #129</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-129/</guid>
      <description>September 30th, 2022 - Instalment #129 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #129.&#xA;We have loads of great new projects this week, with plenty of variety to keep you all interested. We have &amp;ldquo;aws-ecr-cleaner&amp;rdquo;, a great tool to help you manage your container images, &amp;ldquo;dotnet-lambda-sql-server-proxy&amp;rdquo; that shows you how you can use RDS Proxy with SQL Server and why, &amp;ldquo;minecraft-server-dashboard&amp;rdquo; perfect for those running their own minecraft servers, &amp;ldquo;YATAS&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;aws-security-survival-kit&amp;rdquo; for those working on security and governance, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-handler-cookbook&amp;rdquo; useful recipes to get you going, &amp;ldquo;autonomous-driving-data-framework&amp;rdquo; for folks working in the automotive space, and many more - make sure you check all the projects out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #128</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-128/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-128/</guid>
      <description>September 23rd, 2022 - Instalment #128 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #128. I hope some of you were able to catch Derek and myself sharing a peek at this edition, and enjoyed our special guest, Gethin Webster as he walked us through the open source Cloudscape project. If you want to catch up on that event, check out the video here.&#xA;This weeks opens new open source projects include &amp;ldquo;Guardian&amp;rdquo;, a command line tool that produces nice reports on your AWS environments, &amp;ldquo;cdk-scheduler&amp;rdquo;, a new construct that helps you schedule your CDK deployments, &amp;ldquo;terraform-iam-policy-validator&amp;rdquo; a script that helps you validate your Terraform scripts, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-golden-ami-pipeline&amp;rdquo; an example of how to build an automated pipeline to build Amazon Machine Images (AMI&amp;rsquo;s), and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #127</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</guid>
      <description>September 16th, 2022 - Instalment #127 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #127. I hope some of you were able to catch Derek and myself sharing a peek at this edition, and enjoyed as our special guest, AWS Hero Ian Mckay walked us through some of his open source projects. It was very cool indeed, and if you have not yet watched, Ian shares an early glimpse of a new project - so make sure you check that out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #126</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-126/</guid>
      <description>September 9th, 2022 - Instalment #126 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #126. Exciting news this week includes the second episode of the Build on AWS open source show, and the release of a new AWS open source project, event-ruler (more in a bit).&#xA;As always, this weeks newsletter includes more great new open source projects from AWS and the AWS Community. We have &amp;ldquo;aws-integration-for-apache-guacamole&amp;rdquo; that provides a guide of how you can deploy this open source project, &amp;ldquo;xcodeinstall&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you heedlessly install Xcode, &amp;ldquo;soci-snapshotter&amp;rdquo; a very cool project for Container lovers, &amp;ldquo;credentials-fetcher&amp;rdquo; a new Linux demon for those wanting to integrate with Windows environments, &amp;ldquo;imds-credential-server&amp;rdquo; a very nice tool to help you vend AWS credentials, &amp;ldquo;automated-data-analytics-on-aws&amp;rdquo; a new data tool that will help you accelerate time to insights, and &amp;ldquo;event-ruler&amp;rdquo; a very cool new project allowing you to match Rules to Events, and many other projects for you to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #125</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-125/</guid>
      <description>September 2nd, 2022 - Instalment #125 Welcome&#xA;After a couple of weeks off, it is great to welcome to back to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #125. As it has been a couple of weeks, this edition contains even more open source goodness to keep you occupied.&#xA;As always, we kick things off we a round up of new open source projects. Over the past couple of weeks, there were so many that it was hard to select them (I will include the others in next weeks newsletter).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #124</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-124/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-124/</guid>
      <description>August, 12th, 2022 - Instalment #124 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to edition #124 of the AWS open source newsletter. This is a very special edition as this will be the first edition that we cover in the new Build on AWS Open Source fortnight show on twitch.tv/aws. I hope some of you were able to attend, but if not don&amp;rsquo;t worry we will be sharing links to the recording. To keep up to date on future episodes, make sure you follow @buildonopen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #123</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</guid>
      <description>August, 5th, 2022 - Instalment #123 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter episode #123.&#xA;I sometimes speak with builders who are experienced developers but perhaps new to open source. A common question I get asked is what the impact of them working on open source might be on their careers. Whilst it is never a guarantee, open source can be a great career accelerator. I was reminded of that last week when reading the excellent post from Ran Isenberg, who shared his experience in his post How One Open-Source Code Donation Got Me Promoted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #122</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-122/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-122/</guid>
      <description>July 29th, 2022 - Instalment #122 Welcome&#xA;Welcome back to my regular readers and hello to new readers, I hope you will enjoy and come back again to the AWS open source newsletter episode #122.&#xA;This week we have another great collection of community and AWS related open source tools, demos and samples for you to practice your open source four freedoms. &amp;ldquo;rds_auto_encrypt&amp;rdquo; helps you encrypt your Amazon RDS databases, &amp;ldquo;middy-profiler&amp;rdquo; is an interesting looking tool to help you understand performance characteristics of your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;simpleiot&amp;rdquo; is a very nice looking IoT framework to help simplify how you can onboard devices into AWS IoT, &amp;ldquo;aws-secrets-manager-hybrid-secret-replication-from-hashicorp-vault&amp;rdquo; (bit of a mouthful to say that one) helps you synchronise your secrets across different secret providers, &amp;ldquo;automated-forensic-orchestrator-for-amazon-ec2&amp;rdquo; is a very nice reference solution for automating some of your operational security activities, and we have several other projects for you to dive deep into.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #121</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-121/</guid>
      <description>July 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #121 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #121.&#xA;Am super excited about this weeks new projects, including a number of AWS CDK related projects so if you are a fan of AWS CDK then make sure you check them all out. We feature projects such as &amp;ldquo;openrolesanywhere&amp;rdquo;, a proof of concept client for the recently released AWS IAM Roles Anywhere, &amp;ldquo;amazon-redshift-odbc-driver&amp;rdquo; an open source ODBC driver for Amazon Redshift, &amp;ldquo;spot-interruption-simulation&amp;rdquo; a very handy tool to help you test and simulate spot interuptions for your EC2 workloads, &amp;ldquo;magento-ecs-cdk&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy a scalable Magento environment, &amp;ldquo;using-rekognition-to-detect-sounds&amp;rdquo; a very interesting project that will help you hear sounds from your pictures (yes, you did not read that wrong!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #120</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-120/</guid>
      <description>July 15th, 2022 - Instalment #120 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #120.&#xA;The observant will have noticed that it has been two weeks since the last newsletter. We all need some time off, and I spent most of the time cycling around the hills of a new cycle route called King Alfreds Way - highly recommended.&#xA;There has been some great new projects created over the past couple of weeks, and of course I have you covered and have shared them below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #119</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-119/</guid>
      <description>July 1st, 2022 - Instalment #119 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #119.&#xA;This week we feature more new open source projects, such as &amp;ldquo;cdk-bill-bot&amp;rdquo;, a tool that can help you reduce AWS bill surprises, &amp;ldquo;steampipe-mod-aws-perimeter&amp;rdquo; helps you look for resources that are publicly accessible, &amp;ldquo;aws-cloudformation-diagrams&amp;rdquo; is a nice visualisation tool for CloudFormation users, &amp;ldquo;aws-swagger-ui&amp;rdquo; a project to help you set up Swagger UI for API Gateway, &amp;ldquo;kinesis-hot-shard-advisor&amp;rdquo; a handy tool that helps you identify whether you have hot key or hot shard issues on your Kinesis data streams, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #118</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-118/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-118/</guid>
      <description>June 24th, 2022 - Instalment #118 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #118.&#xA;This week we feature more new open source projects, such as &amp;ldquo;seed-farmer&amp;rdquo;, and orchestration tool modelled after GitOps deployments, &amp;ldquo;aws-proton-plugins-for-backstage&amp;rdquo; Backstage plugins for interacting with AWS Proton, &amp;ldquo;dcv-gnome-shell-extension&amp;rdquo; is a GNOME Shell extension to provide functionalities required by NICE DCV, &amp;ldquo;simpleiot-arduino&amp;rdquo; an Arduino library to integrate with the SimpleIOT framework, &amp;ldquo;event-driven-weather-forecasts&amp;rdquo; an event driven weather forecasting demo, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #117</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-117/</guid>
      <description>June 17th, 2022 - Instalment #117 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #117.&#xA;A little behind schedule this week, as I have been speaking at a couple of events this week. It has been good to get back on the stage and to talk and engage with real people. It seems that things are quickly returning back to normal. So this week we have some great new projects for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #116</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-116/</guid>
      <description>June 10th, 2022 - Instalment #116 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #116.&#xA;Another selection of useful and interesting new open source projects for you to try out this week. First up, we have &amp;ldquo;aws-exec&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you do adhoc shell execution in AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;edgy&amp;rdquo; helps you simplify writing tests for Node.js based AWS CloudFront Lambda@Edge functions, &amp;ldquo;cdk-app-cli&amp;rdquo; a really nice cli that every AWS CDK user should know about, &amp;ldquo;Accumulus&amp;rdquo; a great looking reporting tool for AWS Lambda users, &amp;ldquo;sqldef-gitops-cdk&amp;rdquo; is a schema management for several open source databases, &amp;ldquo;log-hub&amp;rdquo; helps you to build your own log analytics tool using OpenSearch, &amp;ldquo;verifiable-controls-evidence-store&amp;rdquo; a very cool solution that builds a mechanism to centrally store findings and results of cloud security controls governing AWS workloads, and many more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #115</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-115/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-115/</guid>
      <description>June 3rd, 2022 - Instalment #115 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #115.&#xA;This week we have another great selection of brand new open source projects for you to explore, including &amp;ldquo;firec&amp;rdquo; a Rust client library for interacting with Firecracker, &amp;ldquo;sfn-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool that helps you quickly build StepFunctions definitions, &amp;ldquo;ssm-cloner&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you replicate across AWS regions your AWS System Manager documents, &amp;ldquo;amazon-lambda-compute-tuning&amp;rdquo; an AWS Lambda function benchmarking tool, &amp;ldquo;aws-iam-root-user-activity-monitor&amp;rdquo; a sample project to help you keep track of your root user, &amp;ldquo;hpc-cost-simulator&amp;rdquo; a tool to help estimate costs running your HPC workloads on AWS, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #114</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-114/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-114/</guid>
      <description>May 27th, 2022 - Instalment #114 Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter #114. This weeks new open source projects feature a variety of community related projects such as &amp;ldquo;instance-scheduler&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you schedule AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;libaws&amp;rdquo; an opinionated tool that helps you simplify creation and deletion of some AWS resources, &amp;ldquo;elasticspot&amp;rdquo; a nice tool to help you reassign elastic IPs, and &amp;ldquo;auto-close-aws-accounts&amp;rdquo; that allows you to close AWS accounts if you are using AWS Organisations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #113</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-113/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-113/</guid>
      <description>May 13th, 2022 - Instalment #113 Newsletter #113.&#xA;A little later than usual this week thanks to KubeCon, #113 of the AWS open source newsletter provides you with yet more new open source projects. &amp;ldquo;aws-iam-utils&amp;rdquo; is a Python library to help you work with IAM, &amp;ldquo;iot-app-kit&amp;rdquo; is a new IoT visualisation framework, &amp;ldquo;s3pathlib-project&amp;rdquo; that provides the Pythonic objective oriented programming (OOP) interface to manipulate AWS S3 object / directory, &amp;ldquo;collaboration-chambers-on-aws&amp;rdquo; which is a cool and very comprehensive project to help you do Scale-Out Computing on AWS, and many more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #112</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-112/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-112/</guid>
      <description>May 13th, 2022 - Instalment #112 Newsletter #112.&#xA;Welcome to this weeks round up of AWS open source news. This weeks new projects features projects such as &amp;ldquo;aws-dataall&amp;rdquo; an open source framework for building a data marketplace, &amp;ldquo;backpack&amp;rdquo; a set of tools to help you work with the AWS Panorama devices, and we have other projects that help you automate DNS tasks, manage game servers, automate data ingestion, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #111</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-111/</guid>
      <description>May 6th, 2022 - Instalment #111 Newsletter #111.&#xA;Welcome to edition #111 of the AWS open source newsletter, a bit later this week but that was so I could pack in even more great open source content. This week we have another round up of new open source projects from the AWS community that include tools to help you manage your AWS CloudFront distributions, resource providers for CloudFormation for Confluent users, managing Amazon Route53 via the command line, a nice tool for Rust developers working with AWS Lambda, a nice tool to help you find your CIDR address ranges, and many more including some great samples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #110</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-110/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-110/</guid>
      <description>April 29th, 2022 - Instalment #110 Newsletter #110.&#xA;Welcome to edition #110 of the AWS open source newsletter. It has been a busy week, with the AWS Summit London happening this week (where I was lucky enough to do a session on Apache Airflow) meaning I am publishing this a little later than I had planned. We have more great new projects this week, including a project that helps make it easier to deploy your static and dynamic applications, a tool that provides help in managing the long term health of your AWS Data Lake, a cool project to help you replicate data from a Kinesis Data Stream across regions, a nice CloudWatch dashboard widget that summarises your CloudFormation stacks, and many more - so check them out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #109</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-109/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-109/</guid>
      <description>April 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #109 Newsletter #109.&#xA;Welcome to edition #109 of the AWS open source newsletter. Big news, I have shaken things up and will be changing the publish date to Friday mornings, starting today with this edition. Over the months I have received some feedback about changing the published date to Fridays, so I am hoping this will give everyone plenty of time to check out the projects, read the posts and provide everyone with something to do over the weekend (if they want!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #108</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-108/</guid>
      <description>April 11th, 2022 - Instalment #108 Newsletter #108.&#xA;A little later the usual as it was a busy week last week, and I was lucky enough to speak at some great events. It certainly seems that things are returning to normality now on the tech events scene, and it was great to meet so many customers and builders who were enthusiastic champions of open source. The AWS Summit season is upon us, with the Brussels summit just gone and Paris Summit happening this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #107</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-107/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-107/</guid>
      <description>April 4th, 2022 - Instalment #107 Newsletter #107.&#xA;Welcome to edition #107 of the AWS open source newsletter, and we have a bumper edition this week packed with more great new open source projects and content for you to consume. Topics featured this week include optimising open source big data tools, developer tooling, case studies and we even some some great open source content for .NET core developers.&#xA;This weeks projects include a really nice handy browser plugin called &amp;ldquo;aws-search-extension&amp;rdquo;, that lets you search and find developer information from the AWS docs, a tool that will help you detect whether you have configured or using dockershim in your Kubernetes clusters, a library to help you integrate Amazon Cognito in your Laravel PHP applications, and plenty more developer tools and sample projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #106</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-106/</guid>
      <description>March 28th, 2022 - Instalment #106 Newsletter #106.&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, and this week we have more great new open source projects to tell you about. We have &amp;ldquo;access-undenied-aws&amp;rdquo;, a tool that helps you better understand your CloudTrail logs and suggest remediation. &amp;ldquo;aws-slack-clickoops-watcher&amp;rdquo; provides you with a way to alert you when changes are made to your AWS environment. &amp;ldquo;kronicle&amp;rdquo; provides a way of illustrating your tech stack automagically, and we have many more tools, demos and sample projects to help get you started on a number of topics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #105</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-105/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-105/</guid>
      <description>March 21st, 2022 - Instalment #105 Newsletter #105.&#xA;Welcome to edition #105 of the AWS open source news and updates, where we bring you the latest open source projects, posts, events, and much more. This weeks new projects include the latest work in progress from AWS Hero Ian Mckay, &amp;ldquo;iamfast&amp;rdquo; is an AWS IAM policy generation tool that is in early stages but promises to be very useful indeed. &amp;ldquo;iasql-engine&amp;rdquo; is a tool that models cloud infrastructure as data, &amp;ldquo;ssm-patch-portal&amp;rdquo; provides a nice gui front end to simplify patching with AWS System Manager, a new crowdsource guide that contains learning resources for AWS, a business intelligence platform built using open source technologies from the NHS, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #104</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-104/</guid>
      <description>March 14th, 2022 - Instalment #104 Newsletter #104.&#xA;Welcome to #104 of the AWS open source news and updates newsletter, bringing you the latest updates from around the AWS and Communities. This week we have yet more great new open source projects, including a Deno runtime for your Lambda functions, data lineage and data testing tools, a performance testing tool for Apache Kafka, an ELT tool for Amazon Redshift, an Amazon S3 archive tool, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #103</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-103/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-103/</guid>
      <description>March 7th, 2022 - Instalment #103 Newsletter #103.&#xA;Welcome to edition #103 of the AWS open source news and updates. This weeks featured new open source projects include botocove (a decorator that helps you run your functions across your AWS accounts easily), functionless (a TypeScript plugin that transforms TypeScript code into Service-to-Service integrations), replibyte (a tool to replicate your PostgreSQL data), aws-security-bulletin-alert (notifies you of new AWS Security Bulletins) and sends out E-Mail notifications via Amazon SES), and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #102</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-102/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-102/</guid>
      <description>Feb 28th, 2022 - Instalment #102 Newsletter #102.&#xA;Welcome to edition #102 of the AWS open source news and updates newsletter, and this week we have a super collection of new open source projects that I am really excited to share. First up we have the AWS DataOps Development Kit, which uses AWS CDK under the covers, and is an open source development framework to help you build data workflows. Threatmapper is an open source cloud native security observability platform, which looks easy to use and has some good visualisations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #101</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-101/</guid>
      <description>Feb 21st, 2022 - Instalment #101 Newsletter #101.&#xA;There is nothing basic and fundamental about edition 101 of the AWS open source newsletter, with another great round up of new open source projects including eks-creation-engine from the folks at Lightspin helping you all to stay safer with this handy tool you should check out, idp-scim-sync to help users of AWS SSO who want to synchronise with their Google Workspace Directory, typecart an analysis tool for proof evolution and many other great projects and sample code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #100</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-100/</guid>
      <description>Feb 14th, 2022 - Instalment #100 Newsletter #100.&#xA;Happy Valentines everyone, and welcome to this landmark 100st edition of this newsletter. This week we celebrate the love that many builders have for open source with more great new open source projects and content. Cuddle up to new projects that will help you build scalable systems, simplify your work with AWS DynamoDB, integrate your .NET applications with OpenSearch, keep on top of your VPC networks, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #99</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-99/</guid>
      <description>Feb 7th, 2022 - Instalment #99 Newsletter #99. While Nena gave you 99 red balloons, I give you the latest version of the AWS open source news letter. This week we feature more great new open source projects including a project to help you with drift detection in your CloudFormation stacks, new Terraform modules, an open-source prometheus exporter, some AWS CDK resources and sample projects and more. This weeks AWS and Community posts cover PostgreSQL, Apache Airflow, AWS CDK, Redis, GraphQL, Apollo GraphQL, Kubernetes, AWS EKS and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #98</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-98/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-98/</guid>
      <description>Jan 31st, 2022 - Instalment #98 Newsletter #98. Welcome to another edition of AWS open source news and updates, featuring more new open source projects. This week, these include eventbridge-assistant (a VScode plugin to help you whilst you are developing with Amazon EventBridge), stratus-red-team (a tool you can use to emulate offensive attack techniques), critter (AWS Config rule integration testing), syne-tune-s3-transfer (an example of how to apply the distributed parameter search library to optimise download performance), karpenter-terraform (a Terraform module to help you automate deployment of karpenter), and a couple of super interesting open source solutions covering last mile delivery and software defined radio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #97</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-97/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-97/</guid>
      <description>Jan 22nd, 2022 - Instalment #97 Newsletter #97.&#xA;Welcome to another edition of the AWS open source newsletter, packed with more great new open source projects, content, and events. This week, we have new projects that help you improve security by de-obfuscating strings, a library to help you automate the configuration of your build pipelines, a new Terraform module, a nice new VSCode plugin that will help you when working with IAM, and several more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #96</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-96/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-96/</guid>
      <description>Jan 17th, 2022 - Instalment #96 Newsletter #96.&#xA;Welcome to another great round up of open source projects, news and great content. This week, we have new open source projects such as Event Catalog (that helps you to discover, explore and document your Event Driven Architectures), AWS Powertools for Lambda TypeScript edition, flowdog (an application/framework for inspection and manipulation of network traffic in AWS VPCs), ai-doorbell (a serverless AI enabled door bell) and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #95</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-95/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-95/</guid>
      <description>Jan 10th, 2022 - Instalment #95 Newsletter #95.&#xA;Feliz Ano and a very happy new year to you all in this first newsletter in 2022. In this weeks update I reflect on some of the interesting stuff I learnt running this newsletter in 2021, before diving into the usual round up of new open source projects, AWS and community blog posts, videos and events. This weeks projects include tfdevops, a tool for Terraform uses to integrate with DevOps Guru, a tool to validate your custom container images on Amazon EMR, a Python wrapper for DynamoDB local and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #94</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-94/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-94/</guid>
      <description>December 20th, 2021 - Instalment #94 Newsletter #94.&#xA;This will be the last newsletter of 2021 before I break for Christmas and New Year. I hope you have found this newsletter a useful resource for finding out about new or interesting open source projects, both from what AWS contributes to, but also from the wider builder and open source developer communities.&#xA;To finish up for 2021 we have more new open source projects, covering Amazon Location Services, AWS Fault Injection Simulator (FIS) experiment templates that are AWS CDK ready, Media Replay Engine (MRE)a really nice project to help you automate the creation of replays, a transcribe, post call analytics solution and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #93</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-93/</guid>
      <description>December 13th, 2021 - Instalment #93 Updated Jan 18th, to remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #93. We took a week off last week to recover from re:Invent, so this week we have extensive coverage of the open source related news and announcements so be sure to check those out. This week we have some great new open source projects, from a project that will help you get started with data meshes, an alternative way to provide internet connectivity to those private subnets, a nice new CDK construct to quickly deploy single page applications and a cool IoT simulator solution which I know I am going to try out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates 92</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-92/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-92/</guid>
      <description>November 29th, 2021 - Instalment #92 Updated 18th Jan, to remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #92. This is the re:Invent edition of the weekly newsletter, and whilst I am not there this year, I will still be covering all the announcements and topics of interest in this and next weeks newsletter.&#xA;Outside of re:Invent, this weeks letter also brings you lots more new open source projects including something for DynamoDB fans, a serverless GraalVM project, a very nice AWS SSO project, new Grafana recipes and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #91</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-91/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-91/</guid>
      <description>November 22nd, 2021 - Instalment #91 Newsletter #91.&#xA;This week I feature eleven new open source projects, covering a diverse array of use cases. From securing your Kubernetes clusters, a couple of nifty Amazon Neptune tools, a Python library that provides state-of-the-art distributed hyper parameter optimising, a sample NFT marketplace and more. This weeks AWS community and AWS content features topics including AWS SAM, Bottlerocket, Babelfish, Apache Airflow, PartiQL, Suricata, Slurm, Apache Kafka, AWS Amplify, PHP and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #90</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-90/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-90/</guid>
      <description>November 15th, 2021 - Instalment #90 Updated, 18th Jan to remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #90.&#xA;Another packed edition of his newsletter, with some great new open source projects such as ploomber (a project to help you build production pipelines for your notebooks), slic-starter (a complete starter project for production-grade serverless applications) and many more interesting projects covering RStudio, Spring Boot, a serverless software vending solution, Kubernetes on the edge and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #89</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-89/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-89/</guid>
      <description>November 8th, 2021 - Instalment #89 Newsletter #89. This week we have another selection of great new projects for you to take a look at. Kicking things off with the latest open source project from Airbnb, ottr, a Public Key Infrastructure framework that handles end-to-end certificate rotations, the other projects include cloudkey, clock-bound, aws-recon, cdk-dia and more. Make sure you check these out.&#xA;As always, we have a wide selection of new blog posts from the AWS and Community bloggers covering topics from Alphafold, BayerCLAW, and Babelfish to OpenSearch, AWS CDK, ffmpeg, Amazon Corretto, Spring Boot, Bottlerocket, Snyk, MariaDB and GitHub actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #88</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-88/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-88/</guid>
      <description>November 1st, 2021 - Instalment #88 Newsletter #88.&#xA;Number 88 symbolises fortune and good luck in Chinese culture (I hope that is correct, so please let me know if that is not) and I hope you will feel you are all the luckier for chancing upon this weeks selection of open source projects and posts.&#xA;This week, the big news was the publishing of the Babelfish repository. Check out the launch post as well as additional content and links to this interesting open source project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #87</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-87/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-87/</guid>
      <description>October 25th, 2021 - Instalment #87 Newsletter #87.&#xA;As we approach Halloween (or Dia de los Muertos/All Saints as I remember it), rest assured there is nothing scary in this weeks round up of all things open source on AWS. This weeks projects include a project that helps you implement a GitOps workflow that includes Crossplane and Argo CD, and a static analysis tool for CloudFormation templates. We have some great blog posts this week, featured topics include Apache Kafka, StackGres, Spinnaker, OpenShift, Envoy, Porting Assistant for .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #86</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-86/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-86/</guid>
      <description>October 18th, 2021 - Instalment #86 updated Jan 18th, to remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #86.&#xA;This week we have a very broad variety of topics. Starting off with some fresh open source projects such as cfn-diagram, aws-jwt-verify, damo, aws-dotnet-deploy, automated-account-configuration, BayerCLAW and more. For mains, we have new AWS and community authored posts on MySQL, OpenSearch, .NET, miniwdl, OpenMRS, Apache Hudi, Apache Spark, ROS, cdk8s, Jax, Deep Graph Library and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #85</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-85/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-85/</guid>
      <description>October 11th, 2021 - Instalment #85 Newsletter #85.&#xA;This week we have an interesting gaming flavour to this newsletter, with a couple of projects that are influenced or are directly related to gaming. We also have other new open source projects including one that shows you how you can run an OpenVSCode Server for AWS Graviton2. This weeks blog post and tutorials cover Apache Airflow, Apache Spark, Apache Kafka, Apache Ranger, Apache Flink, OpenSearch, Apache Lucene, PostgreSQL, AWS CDK, and Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates 84</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-84/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-84/</guid>
      <description>October 4th, 2021 - Instalment #84 updated Jan 18th, to remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #84.&#xA;Welcome to issue #84 of this newsletter, and we have more great new open source projects for you this week. We have a couple of great security/compliance/governance tools that will help you with security in cloudgraphdev and (the amazingly named) wonk, placebo, a tool to help you mock tests, a new cli from AWS to help you simplify those of you working with genomics workloads, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #83</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-83/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-83/</guid>
      <description>September 27th, 2021 - Instalment #83 Newsletter #83.&#xA;Welcome to issue #83 of this newsletter, and more great new open source projects to check out. For infrastructure as code practitioners we have several projects for both CDK and Terrafrom, a CI/CD project to help you scale GitHub Actions runners, a simple hosting project with some nice features you can use as a baseline for your own project, a reference architecture for data analytics on AWS with some comprehensive CDK stacks you can inspect and borrow for your own, a project to help you visualise some of your key cloud metrics and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #82</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-82/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-82/</guid>
      <description>September 20th, 2021 - Instalment #82 Newsletter #82.&#xA;Welcome to issue #82 of this newsletter, bringing you the latests updates on open source on AWS. This weeks featured new projects include cdk-nag (helping CDK developers to shift left and check their stacks against best practices), cfn-alarms (a nice tool to automate the creation of your CloudWatch alarms), aws-lambda-adapter (a project to help accelerate your web applications to serverless), as well as some new open source solutions including aws-security-hub-automated-response-and-remediation and eks-preventative-controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #81</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-81/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-81/</guid>
      <description>September 13th, 2021 - Instalment #81 Updated 18th Jan, remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #81.&#xA;Welcome new and existing readers of this newsletter to another edition with plenty to excite you. This weeks brand new open source projects include some great new AWS CDK constructs to help you with things such as Apache Airflow, a tool to help you with your IAM policies, a really nice tool to explore and interact with AWS SQS and something for Minecraft fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #80</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-80/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-80/</guid>
      <description>September 6th, 2021 - Instalment #80 Newsletter #80.&#xA;So what delights does #80 of this newsletter offer this week? We have plenty of new open source projects, such as aws-o11y-recipes (observability recipes), dassana-io (contextual alerts), sgCheckup (security), aws-lambda-scheduler (developer tool to simplify scheduling of AWS Lambda functions), aacli (AWS cli authentication/SSO) as well as Terraform modules and AWS open source solutions covering Hugging Face, reporting on your AWS accounts and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #79</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-79/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-79/</guid>
      <description>August 27th, 2021 - Instalment #79 Newsletter #79.&#xA;The combination of having been away on PTO for the past few weeks, and this coming Monday being a national holiday in the UK, I thought I would post the newsletter today. Covering nearly three weeks, a lot has happened so there is a lot to cover.&#xA;We have 17 new open source projects and solutions, including EventBridge Canon, an essential project if you are working with event driven architectures on AWS, kics a security scanning tool for your IaC, open source solutions such as aws-security-analytics-bootstrap and amazon-msk-with-apache-kafka-streams-api, and other new projects like aws-python-utilities, snap-xcompile, riFT, rds_iamauth_proxy, aws-simple-websocket, ecs-external-instance-network-sentry and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #78</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-78/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-78/</guid>
      <description>August 2nd, 2021 - Instalment #78 Newsletter #78.&#xA;This is the last newsletter for the next three weeks, as I will be taking some time off and shutting down my laptop. I will look forward to bringing you a very full edition when I return, but in the meantime enjoy another great collection of open source projects and blog posts to help you get the most out of open source on AWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #77</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-77/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-77/</guid>
      <description>26th July, 2021 - Instalment #77 Newsletter #77.&#xA;This week we have more new open source projects including schema-manager, maildog, ddbcereal, ecr-scan-reporter and more. This weeks AWS and community blog posts cover topics such as PartiQL, ConsoleMe, Yor, Kubernetes, Debezium, Apache Kafka, Apache Spark, Redis, HPC and more. Also, don&amp;rsquo;t miss the great video on getting up and running with Amazon EMR on Apache Airflow.&#xA;Observability (o11y) newsletter&#xA;If you had not already signed up for this, then perhaps now is a great time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #76</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-76/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-76/</guid>
      <description>19th July, 2021 - Instalment #76 Newsletter #76.&#xA;This week, we have new oss projects such as ecs-files-composer, lucid-dynamodb, kubectl-trace, tailscale-layer and more. AWS and community blog posts featuring OpenSearch, Kubernetes, COBOL, Jamulus, Firecracker, Apache Hudi, Apache Kakfa, Apache Flink, Redis and more. In the videos section we catch up with a couple of the sessions from the Airflow Summit and finally, some new events for your diary.&#xA;Celebrating open source contributors The articles posted in this series are only possible thanks to contributors and project maintainers and so I would like to shout out and thank those folks who really do power open source and enable us all to build on top of what they have created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #75</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-75/</guid>
      <description>12th July, 2021 - Instalment #75 Newsletter #75.&#xA;This week we have a bumper edition, due to the fact I did not publish last week and it looks like everyone has been very busy. We have new open source projects include a light weight Java client, a tool to help you manage your AWS resources and some sample applications to help you get started with location based services, Bottlerocket and algorithmic trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news/updates #74</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-newsupdates-74/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-newsupdates-74/</guid>
      <description>28th June, 2021 - Instalment #74 Newsletter #74.&#xA;This week we have new open source projects that help you access your AWS EFS data without the need for a VPN, a new Red Team security tool that is in the very early stages and a number of new AWS projects to help you easily deploy open source projects such as Nextcloud or manage your own SQL Server deployments. Community and AWS posts covering Apache Airflow, Rust, Prometheus, DevOps, Apache Spark, R Studio, Grafana Loki and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #73</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-73/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-73/</guid>
      <description>21st June, 2021 - Instalment #73 updated 18th, Jan to remove dead link&#xA;Newsletter #73.&#xA;This week&amp;rsquo;s new projects include a project than can help you reduce your costs if you are running Amazon EKS workloads, an AWS CDK pattern to help you easily create internal and external access points for your applications, a GraphQL solution and some sample AWS projects. We have community and AWS authored posts featuring Kubernetes, Apache Flink, Firecracker, OpenSearch, Apache Tinkerpop, Apache Kafka, as well as .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #72</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-72/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-72/</guid>
      <description>14th June, 2021 - Instalment #72 Newsletter #72.&#xA;This week we have new open source projects such as Lift, that makes it super easy to deploy applications to production, a couple of new mods for the Steampipe project that let you do cost optimisation and security auditing, a nice project for tmux fans as well as a project that will get you started with ECS Anywhere. Community and AWS posts covering security, DevOps and IoT/Robotics, as well as Kubernetes, Open Shift, Apache Airflow, Linux and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #71</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-71/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-71/</guid>
      <description>7th June, 2021 - Instalment #71 Newsletter #71.&#xA;This week we have a number of security related projects, covering reference/best practice deployments of open source security tools as well as new tools that will help you identify misconfigured assets. Another interesting project this week is moot, a serverless project to help yo simplify your deployments. On top of the new projects, we have some great community and AWS blog posts on Kubernetes, OpenSearch, Eventbridge Atlas, Keycloak, Apache Kafka, SQLAlchemy, AWS Copilot, OpenShift and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #70</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-70/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-70/</guid>
      <description>1st June, 2021 - Instalment #70 Due to it being a bank holiday in the UK, Newsletter #70 is a day later than usual.&#xA;Make sure you check out this weeks &amp;ldquo;Quick Updates&amp;rdquo; as there are some updates that I know a lot of people will be happy about, and I always share great nuggets that sometimes folk miss. More great projects this week, from iamzero which helps you simplify your identity and access management, PMapper that you will find helpful for identifying risks in your IAM configurations, an AWS CDK construct to help you deploy a VSCode server, Orkestra, a super nice project that lets you create workflows using Lambda functions a la Apache Airflow and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #69</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-69/</guid>
      <description>May 24th, 2021 - Instalment #69 Newsletter #69.&#xA;This week we celebrate more new open source projects, covering tools that can help you lock down and monitor your IAM policies, reference solutions that make it easy to deploy a number of open source projects, and a great tool to help you monitor/debug your serverless functions. On top of that the usual round up of community and AWS blog posts, featuring lots of updates on Kubernetes, performance tuning HTTP on EC2, LLVM, Apache Kafka, Triton inference, the next version of Cloudformation guard, Bottlerocket, AWS Graviton2, Tensorflow and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #68</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-68/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-68/</guid>
      <description>May 17th, 2021 - Instalment #68 Newsletter #68.&#xA;What better way that to celebrate my 100th post on dev.to with the latest AWS open source news and updates. This week we have posts covering Rust, OpenSearch, SaaS Boost, Apache Airflow, Kubernetes, Taurus, Spring Boot, Jenkins, GraphQL, Redis and more. If you are looking for projects, make sure you check out SaaS Boost which generated a lot of buzz last week, as well as the first beta of OpenSearch, sls-test-tools, aws-assume-role-lib and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #67</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-67/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-67/</guid>
      <description>May 10th, 2021 - Instalment #67 Newsletter #67.&#xA;This week more great open source projects for you to get stuck into. The big news last week was the release in alpha of the new Rust SDK for AWS, so make sure you check that out if you are exploring the world of Rust. We also have a couple of interesting new projects on awslabs, always a great place to explore if you have the time, awsclii a nice little tool that generates groovy ascii graphics as well as some significant updates to some projects I have covered in earlier newsletters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #66</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-66/</guid>
      <description>May 4th, 2021 - Instalment #66 Updated Jan 18th, to remove dead links&#xA;Newsletter #66.&#xA;This week we have a really outstanding collection of new open source projects, including eventbridge-atlas, ecsk, spotinfo, pecos and more, so make sure you spend some time checking those out. Following on from CDK Day, we have plenty of great posts for CDK fans. As always, there are lots of great community and AWS blog posts covering event driven architectures, containers, big data, and so happy to see the AWS DeepRacer open source announcements last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #65</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-65/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-65/</guid>
      <description>April, 26th, 2021 - Instalment #65 Newsletter #65.&#xA;This week we have new projects covering security, AWS CDK, serverless and a very handy tool if you find yourself having to record your screen to do demos and wondering how to make sure you do not disclose sensitive information such as your AWS credentials. We have AWS and community blog posts covering Kubernetes, AWS Copilot, Rust, GraphQL, Apache Airflow, Linux, we have a couple of workshops on AWS Greengrass v2 and Observability on AWS and much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #64</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-64/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-64/</guid>
      <description>April, 19th, 2021 - Instalment #64 Newsletter #64.&#xA;Another great selection of posts this week, starting off with the announcement last week of OpenSearch and OpenSearch Dashboards, the name of the community driven open source fork of Elasticsearch and Kibana. We have a great selection of community posts covering topics such as Apache Zeppelin, Rust, OpenJDK as well as an exciting new project called Lift to watch out for. Some great new open source projects including how to run Haskell on AWS Lambda, a nice project to make it easy to run EKS Distro on your desktop, so make sure you check those out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #63</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-63/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-63/</guid>
      <description>April, 12th, 2021 - Instalment #63 Newsletter #63.&#xA;No newsletter last week due to the holidays, which means that this week we have a bumper edition. Check out the AWS CDK content this week, as there is both lots of it, but also all if it is great. We then have some great content if you are into containers, and the usual round up of other open source posts from AWS and the community covering topics such as Selenium, Apache Airflow, Apache Flink, GraphQL, Java and much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #62</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-62/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-62/</guid>
      <description>March 29th, 2021 - Instalment #62 Newsletter #62.&#xA;This week we have some really interesting new projects for you to take a look at, including someones first. We have cli tools to make it easier to work with the recently announced ECS Exec, to a serverless security tool, a very nice project that incorporates AWS CDK as part of an ArchOps project and more. We also have some great reads for you this week - check out the back story of Jupyter from Matt, a few posts on how AWS and Hugging Face are working together, some nice posts for you DevOps enthusiasts and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #61</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-61/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-61/</guid>
      <description>March 22nd, 2021 - Instalment #61 Newsletter #61.&#xA;This week we have a lot of love for Apache projects, covering Apache Lucene, Parquet, Airflow, Cassandra and HBase, with a couple of must read posts. On top of that, we have more new open source projects, including a couple of curated lists of essential resources as well as some new open source tools from AWS. Finally, the usual round up of open source posts from the community and AWS, as well as a couple of videos and short updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #60</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-60/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-60/</guid>
      <description>March 15th, 2021 - Instalment #60 Newsletter #60.&#xA;This week is packed with posts for data lovers, with posts covering Presto, Apache Airflow and Apache Hudi, we have some Java goodies in the form of a nice deep dive on Heapothesys and a couple of posts on Kotlin, a couple of great whitepapers - the first will help you move your workloads (and open source projects) to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, and the other is an update to the Redis whitepaper, and the usual round up of community and AWS related posts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #59</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-59/</guid>
      <description>March 8th, 2021 - Instalment #59 Newsletter #59. This week we have a really great selection of open source projects for you to take a look at. Quail, not just a fancy egg you enjoy on those special occasions but an interesting project that helps you easily provision resources for your developers was my pick from a very good bunch. Aside from that, the usual round up of fresh blog posts from AWS and the community, some new events that are happening later this week and next and a new newsletter for you to sign up to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #58</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-58/</guid>
      <description>March 1st, 2021 - Instalment #58 Newsletter #58.&#xA;This week we have posts covering some of my favourite topics, AWS Graviton and AWS CDK, we have some new events to check out, more great videos from the Containers on the couch folk, as well as the usual round up of new open source projects, AWS and community related posts and quick updates.&#xA;Before we crack on, why not start by reading this post, The real value of open source in the cloud that Matt Asay wrote last week that talks about the freedom and choice that open source provides, whether that is in the Cloud or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #57</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-57/</guid>
      <description>February 22nd, 2021 - Instalment #57 Newsletter #57.&#xA;This week we have another great selection of content to share with you. Starting off with a look at open source at AWS, which is a must read this week, we meander through a look at a write up of the open source technology stack that supported Fossdem a few weeks ago. Then it is off to the usual round up of latest open source projects, blog posts from the community and AWS as well as a look at some quick updates, videos and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #56</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-56/</guid>
      <description>February 15th, 2021 - Instalment #56 Newsletter #56.&#xA;This week we have the latest update on the Elasticsearch/Kibana fork, events for your diary, the usual round up of blog posts and new open source projects as well as white papers, a nice selection of videos, workshops and case studies. Make sure you read the Rust Foundation blog post this week and check out Didier&amp;rsquo;s post on running a serverless mainframe&amp;hellip;well kind of!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #55</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-55/</guid>
      <description>February 8th, 2021 - Instalment #55 Newsletter #55.&#xA;Another newsletter full of great content for you this week. Make sure you read the essential read this week, Rights Ratchet Model, keep on top of the latest news on the fork of Elasticsearch, some events for your diary, more great videos, a new workshop and of course the usual open source projects and posts from the community and AWS. Pick of the week has to be Ian Mckay&amp;rsquo;s new open source project, iamlive - make sure you check it out in the projects section below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #54</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-54/</guid>
      <description>February 1st, 2021 - Instalment #54 Newsletter #54. Lots to choose from this week. Catch up with the latest from the Open Distro for Elasticsearch community, an event for your diary in the shape of Innovate AI/ML where I will be covering open source tools in your AI/ML pipeline, and the usual round up of AWS and community open source posts. We have some great open source projects that you need to check out - from tools and utilities that solve real pain points to complete solutions you can use as the base for your projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #53</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-53/</guid>
      <description>January 25th, 2021 - Instalment #53 Newsletter #53&#xA;This weeks newsletter has another great variety of posts and projects for you to check out. First up though, and probably the most important news from last week was the announcement around how AWS is looking to keep Elasticsearch and Kibana open source (read the post below). In addition to that news, we have some interesting projects for builders interested in infrastructure as code, a couple of great benchmarking posts, including another great AWS Graviton2 story and my new favourite open source project, Apache Airflow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #52</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-52/</guid>
      <description>January 18th, 2021 - Instalment #52 Newsletter #52&#xA;This week we have a number of posts covering AWS Cloud Development Kit, (AWS CDK) as well as Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA) which you should check out (ok, I&amp;rsquo;ll admit I might have been involved in some of those) as well as a couple of interesting projects. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the summary of re:Invent from last week - still plenty of time to catch up with the on demand videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.51</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no51/</guid>
      <description>January 11th, 2021 - Instalment #51 Welcome to Newsletter #51. This week we have a carefully selected group of blog posts, projects and more. Make sure you check out this weeks must read post on how to prepare and plan for migrating your existing .NET workloads to .NET Core. We have a couple of new projects that you need to take a look at; first of we have Querypal, essential for Amazon Athena users, and following that make sure you check out the preview of the MySQL JDBC driver (in Quick updates section).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.50</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no50/</guid>
      <description>January 4th, 2021 - Instalment #50 Newsletter #50 and the first one this year. I hope you all had a good break over the festive season. I am busy catching up with all the open source posts, projects, case studies and more, much of which I have shared this week. I have also covered what is happening next week with the concluding week of re:Invent - plenty more open source sessions to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.49</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no49/</guid>
      <description>December 21st - Instalment #49 Week No.49 and this will be the last newsletter this year. It is good to go out on a high, and this week we have a round up of the third week of re:Invent, following Dr Werner Vogels&amp;rsquo;s keynote and announcements. There are plenty of great posts related to those launches as well as re:Invent sessions to find out more. We also have the usual round up of blog posts, case studies, videos and open source projects which you can think of as stocking fillers as we head into Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.48</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no48/</guid>
      <description>December 13th - Instalment #48 Week No.48 going into the final week of re:Invent this year (don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we still have more sessions in the 2nd week of 2021) we have another great selection of posts. This week a favourite project of mine gets a lot of love, as well as a roundup of the second week of re:Invent. If that was not enough for you, then I throw in some new open source projects which you will definitely need to check out, with some really great ones including the latest project from Netflix that might make you Weep!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.47</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no47/</guid>
      <description>December 7th - Instalment #47 Week No.47 and with the first week of re:Invent over, it was good to see so many great open source related announcements. You can expected detailed coverage of those in this weeks roundup, including links to the various sessions and blog posts that have been published this week to support those announcements. If that was not enough, this week still has a great round up of other open source blog posts, some really interesting open source projects and of course, more posts from the community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 46</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-46/</guid>
      <description>November 30th - Instalment #46 Week No.46 and this week marks the beginning of re:Invent 2020 so expect a lot of re:Invent related content in this episode and the next couple. re:Invent has not stopped the relentless march of great open source blog posts, projects and more this week, and we have some great stuff this week including&amp;hellip;the launch of Amazon Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow, an unmissable post on Rust from Matt Asay, a bumper selection of Elasticsearch updates this week, a new project from the Amazon Neptune team and a couple of fantastic videos, one covering AWS CDK and projen and the other kube-bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.45</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no45/</guid>
      <description>November 23rd - Instalment #45 Week No.45 and this is the last edition before re:Invent so look out this week for some blog posts sharing news about the open source track and open source sessions at re:Invent this year. This week we have another great selection of posts, projects and more. Make sure you check out the Karpenter project that was announced last week during AWS Container Day at KubeCon, a great selection of Kubernetes/container related posts and some more great posts on AWS Graviton2 and Nitro Enclaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.44</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no44/</guid>
      <description>November 16th - Instalment #44 Week No.44 and in a weekend just gone where Lewis Hamilton was crowned the world champion for the seventh time, it was interesting to learn that he has used the number 44 since 2014. From the grand prix to the grand prize of open source, and this week we have open source posts from a number of the AWS Hero communities, Spring Boot fans and a selection for those interested in GraphQL as well as the usual round up of projects, events and case studies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.43</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no43/</guid>
      <description>November 9th - Instalment #43 Week No.43 or 101011 if you prefer binary notation. This week we have the usual collection of open source projects, blog posts, events, case studies and workshops. Of note this week is the GA of the Lambda Powertools for Java, news of the announcement last week of the new RabbitMQ message broker service, more AWS Nitro Enclave goodness, a brand new workshop from Nader Dabit and more events and webinars for your diary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.42</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no42/</guid>
      <description>November 2nd - Instalment #42 Week No.42 - 42 may be the answer to the ultimate question of Life, the Universe and Everything, but for today it is just the latest roundup of all the open source news, projects, events, case studies related to AWS. This week we have a great case study from Intuit and their journey to Kubernetes, we have a couple of nice updates from the Open Distro for Elasticsearch, sleemo a nice new open source GraphQL framework and the Stelligent University, an open source curriculum to help bootstrap your learning on AWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.41</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no41/</guid>
      <description>October 26th - Instalment #41 Episode No.41 - As we approach Halloween this week, there is nothing scary or frightening in this episode, just a shockingly good amount of new open source projects, blog posts, case studies and events to add to your diary. Last week was dominated by the Open Distro for Telemetry preview announcement (read all about that in a minute) but there is also great stuff such as the unboxing of HashiCorp&amp;rsquo;s Waypoint by the Containers from the Couch team, something for Java folk and another Graviton2 post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No.40</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no40/</guid>
      <description>October 19th - Instalment #40 Week No.40 - if life begins at 40 then I am pleased that this newsletter has reached this milestone. We are only just getting started, and since producing this in January we have covered over 800 articles and over 300 different authors covering open source projects and topics. This week we have the usual round up of new projects, a variety of blog post topics including a couple of unmissable posts on how you can combine Rancher, Kubernetes and the AWS Snowball family of products for some interest &amp;rsquo;edge of edge&amp;rsquo; deployment models and a great post covering an old favourite of mine, AWS DeepRacer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast - open source builders: Arpit Mohan</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/podcast---open-source-builders-arpit-mohan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/podcast---open-source-builders-arpit-mohan/</guid>
      <description>In this podcast I speak with Arpit Mohan, CTO and Co Founder of Appsmith an innovative no/low code project that can accelerate how you build solutions for your customers. In this session I chat with Arpit and ask him about his journey in tech, the leap from hardware to software, the ups and downs of startups and of course open source software. Here are some of the points we cover in this podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 39</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-39/</guid>
      <description>October 12th - Instalment #39 Week No.39 - The 39 Steps is a pretty famous film, a spy thriller if you are into those types of films and I recently found out that the name came from a location not too far from me. I am pleased to say that episode 39 of this newsletter is equally thrilling, combining the usual mix of new open source projects (including one so fresh, it is still warm to the touch), blog posts, case studies and events for you to check out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 38</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-38/</guid>
      <description>October 5th - Instalment #38 Week No.38 and following on from the very first CDK Day, there is plenty of AWS CDK stuff including a link to the recording of the event if you missed it. Aside from that, there is the usual round up of blog posts, including another excellent post featuring honeycomb.io doing some benchmarks on running AWS Graviton2 instance types on a number of open source projects, the latest new AWS related open source projects, events, case studies and we also have a workshop for you, covering how to get started with TorchServe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 37</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-37/</guid>
      <description>September 28th - Instalment #37 Week No.37 and plenty of open source goodness to sink your teeth into this week. We have the usual projects round up, including projects to help you work with your AWS Secrets via the CLI or quickly spin up AWS infrastructure, we have posts covering topics such as Spring Boot, tagging of AWS resources and a must read post on Kubernetes and then finally we have the usual round up of AWS open source goodies and case studies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 36</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-36/</guid>
      <description>September 21st - Instalment #36 Week No.36 and this week have the usual round up of open source goodies, but I do want to call out the Lambda Power Tool UI project and the AWS Graviton2 posts this week as must reads. There is also a a couple of excellent deep dives from Alex Casalboni on optimising Lambda and from Blair Hudson, head of data engineering at Faethm AI. Finally, learn more about how Boston is tackling urban deforestation with the use of open data sets, machine learning and is open sourcing the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 35</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-35/</guid>
      <description>September 14th - Instalment #35 Week No.35, this week we have more great blog posts, projects, events and case studies for you. This week we have the first open source themed Dev Day (see below) which is something I encourage you all to check out as some AWS&amp;rsquo;s best speakers will be covering some great open source topics. As always, thanks for everyone who contributes these posts - please follow them to keep up with future posts and updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 34</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-34/</guid>
      <description>September 7th - Instalment #34 Week No.34, and another packed issue with some great posts, projects and events covering all your favourite open source projects. This week there has been a lot of focus on Bottlerocket, which went GA last week, so plenty of stuff to read as well as several videos to watch. There are a couple of events happening later this week, so check the events just a little below and save the date in your diary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 33</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-33/</guid>
      <description>August 31st - Instalment #33 Week No.33, and as we come to the end of the summer season with people returning back from holiday, it is good to see that there has been no slow down in open source activities. This week we have plenty of blog posts, projects for you to check out and customer stories.&#xA;We also have a growing list of events to add to your diary, so make sure you check these out too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 32</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-32/</guid>
      <description>August 24th - Instalment #32 Week No.32 and after two weeks taking some time off visiting sunny Scotland, I return refreshed with a bumper edition with the pick of posts from the past few weeks. As always, some great posts and projects as well as some events you might want to add to your diary and a few customer case studies for you to check out.&#xA;Your feedback matters! I have put together a short feedback survey, which I would ask you to take - it will take no more than 2 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 31</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-31/</guid>
      <description>August 3rd - Instalment #31 Week No.31 and the last update for a few weeks. I will be taking a break from all things open source and tech, seeking solace in nature and recharging my curiosity batteries for the next couple of weeks, so there will be no updates August 10th and 17th. In the meantime, enjoy another packed edition - there appears no slow down when it comes to open source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 30</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-30/</guid>
      <description>July 27th - Instalment #30 Week No.30 and another week of great projects and posts. We have a new open source builder story, the usual selection of projects from robotics to compliance/governance tools and blog posts that cover topics from machine learning to security and serverless. Another good selection of cases studies and customers who are using open source to make a difference as well as some events you should check out and add to your diary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast - open source builders: Justin Garrison</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/podcast---open-source-builders-justin-garrison/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/podcast---open-source-builders-justin-garrison/</guid>
      <description>In this podcast I speak with Justin Garrison, Developer Advocate in the Containers team at AWS, and ask him about his journey in open source.&#xA;From user to contributor&#xA;According to PwC&amp;rsquo;s annual CEO Survey (which you can find easily enough via your preferred search tool), one of the top challenges keeping CEO&amp;rsquo;s up at night is how to tackle their digital skills shortage. In fact, 74% were concerned about the availability of key skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 29</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-29/</guid>
      <description>July 20th - Instalment #29 Week No.29, and another epic edition packed with lots of great projects and posts, as well as a larger than normal number of case studies this week. Pick of the bunch from me (always hard) is the walkthrough of the CDK Patterns from Matt, the customer case studies and the finala and inframap projects. Remember, if you have a project you want me to mention or talk about, then please reach out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 28</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-28/</guid>
      <description>July 13th - Instalment #28 Week No.28, and this week we have another fantastic collection of open source posts covering robotics, containers, serverless, machine learning and more. I cover a number of projects you can get stuck into, including robotics projects and resources, a continuous machine learning project posts and the usual collection of indispensable projects that you will wonder how you ever managed without. Finally there are some events you might want to put in your diary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 27</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-27/</guid>
      <description>Updated, 18th Jan to remove dead links&#xA;July 6th - Instalment #27 Week No.27, and as the days start getting shorter, these weekly newsletters just keep getting longer. There is so much activity and energy in open source, and I am continuously amazed at what new stuff I unearth and uncover.&#xA;This week we have more machine learning goodness, containers, a splattering of serverless, some very interesting .NET updates as well as some more esoteric articles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 26</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-26/</guid>
      <description>June 29th - Instalment #26 No.26 and officially the half way point of the year. There has been no let up in open source projects and posts. This week we have machine learning deep dives and projects, including a reinforcement learning project that might help you win at Poker, security, serverless and modern application posts.&#xA;It was really good to catch up this week with Arpit Mohan, CTO and co-founder of Appsmith about the topic of open source, growing awareness and different licensing models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 25</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-25/</guid>
      <description>June 22nd - Instalment #25 No.25 is another packed edition with plenty of interesting projects and stories for you to read, whether you are into machine learning, robots, cutting your teeth on code or looking at how to automate and secure your deployments, there is something for you.&#xA;As we past the summer equinox and very close to the half way point of the year, I wanted to share some of the data I have collected over the past six months when putting together this digest and speaking with the builders and business&amp;rsquo; using open source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 24</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-24/</guid>
      <description>June 15th - Instalment #24 Another expansive instalment in No. 24, as we approach the half way point of the year. In this episode we have a number of PHP related posts, fitting as it rapidly approaches its 25th anniversary. If you are a PHP builder, then keep your eyes/ears posted, as we have something special for you soon. Aside from PHP, we have some great new projects as well as important new releases for existing ones that you need to know about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 23</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-23/</guid>
      <description>June 8th - Instalment #23 Episode 23 - I was reminded this week that I have now posted over 30 posts to dev.to since I joined the platform late last year. I am currently putting together some stats that I will share with you around the breakdown of various open source topics I have seen over that time. Watch this space.&#xA;This week I have added a Retro section as one of the things that keeps coming up is cool open source projects that are not new, but I had never heard of before and are getting new contributions or releases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates No. 22</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-22/</guid>
      <description>June 1st - Instalment #22 Episode 22, and another great collection of open source stories, updates and projects. Whether it learning about new open source application run times like Deno, impactful projects like AutoSpotting that might help you reduce your costs or those simple but every so useful projects that you just could not get by without, such as ssosync or EKStender.&#xA;Please contact me with your AWS related open source projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open sources new and updates - No. 21</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-sources-new-and-updates---no-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-sources-new-and-updates---no-21/</guid>
      <description>May 25th - Instalment #21 Episode 21, another full edition. We have some significant announcements of new projects from Uber, a variety of different posts and code for those interested in containers, plenty of serverless goodness and as always, some great Amplify and AWS AppSync posts. We also have a couple of posts on how to get some open source projects you might be using up and running on AWS. Before you dive in, a couple of things you check out first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - No. 20</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-20/</guid>
      <description>May 18th - Instalment #20 Episode 20, another packed episode with plenty to check out, and some really great announcements and projects to share. With that, let&amp;rsquo;s get started with one of our big announcements last week.&#xA;cdk8s&#xA;The big news this week though was the launch of CDK for Kubernetes, an open-source software development framework for defining Kubernetes applications and reusable abstractions using familiar programming languages and rich object-oriented APIs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open sources new and updates - No. 19</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-sources-new-and-updates---no-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-sources-new-and-updates---no-19/</guid>
      <description>May 11th - Instalment #19 Episode 19, and this week&amp;rsquo;s edition is bursting at the seams with probably the biggest amount of news and updates to share (hence the later posting). Looks like everyone has been busy, and there were some things I had to leave out for another time.&#xA;Before I get started though, I think it is worth reflecting on this blog post by Matt Asay, The most important part of an open source project, where he talks about the value of all contributions in open source projects, not just the developers cutting code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open sources news and updates - No. 18</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-sources-news-and-updates---no-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-sources-news-and-updates---no-18/</guid>
      <description>May 4th - Instalment #18 Episode 18, is the open source Force strong in you?&#xA;A post from colleague Matt Asay this week, Remembering when open source is fun made me think about the first open source projects I got my hands on (Apache httpd server, back in 1998). Good times indeed, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until later that I did my first contribution (a security module for Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Confluence to enable SSO).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - Instalment No. 17</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---instalment-no-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---instalment-no-17/</guid>
      <description>April 27th - Instalment #17 Episode 17, and as we leave April and head into May, we have a bumper edition with some very interesting new open source projects that AWS launched this week, TorchServe and Amazon Keyspaces as well as the usual round up of interesting projects, blog posts and other essential reading materials to keep you up to speed with the world of AWS and open source.&#xA;Celebrate open source contributors The articles posted in this series are only possible thanks to contributors and project maintainers and so I would like to shout out and thank those folks who really do power open source and enable us all to build on top of what they have created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - No. 16</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-16/</guid>
      <description>April 20th - Instalment #16 Episode 16, and like most folk confining myself to my home has provided me with lots of time to search the four corners of the internet to bring you all the latest news, updates and interesting things happening where open source meets AWS. This week I want to share a couple of posts in which both Amazon and open source developers and communities are helping to tackle the COVID pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - No. 15</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-15/</guid>
      <description>April 13th - Instalment #15 Episode 15, the Easter special and even though this is a holiday in most of Europe, that was not going to stop me posting this weeks latest and greatest updates from the confluence of AWS and open source.&#xA;Celebrate open source contributors The articles posted in this series are only possible thanks to contributors and project maintainers and so I would like to shout out and thank those folks who really do power open source and enable us all to build on top of what they have created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - No. 14</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-14/</guid>
      <description>April 6th - Instalment #14 Episode 14, and yet more abundance of open source to share with you. Fourteen is an interesting number, and very quickly googling this, I learnt that the number fourteen has a number of interesting facts: the moon waxes for fourteen days and then wanes for fourteen days, a golf player can have no more than fourteen clubs in their caddy, it is the atomic number for silicon and for those who enjoy their open source with the literature, 14 is also the number of lines in a sonnet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - No. 13</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no-13/</guid>
      <description>March 30th - Instalment #13 Episode 13, lucky for some, superstitious for others. I can promise you no superstitious when you read this, nothing but the finest open source news and updates from around the globe and hopefully a few projects that you will find useful. First though, let us celebrate those people that without them, this newsletter would be just an empty vessel. Interesting to see a higher than normal number of new projects and first time projects this week which is awesome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates - No.12</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates---no12/</guid>
      <description>March 23rd - Instalment #12 Episode 12 in the series of open source news and updates on AWS brings you another mixed bag of treats. I wanted to start this instalment however with some of the projects that are looking to help respond to the current COVID-19 situation. You can read more about some of the initiatives at Amazon in the blog post that shows how we are helping researchers and scientists accelerate diagnostics, research and testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #11</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-11/</guid>
      <description>March 16th - Instalment #11 Another packed weekly instalment of open source goodness for you, including a very hot announcement we made this week on Bottlerocket. Whether you are interested in security, devOps or the latest open source projects that run on AWS or make your life easier, then read on as there is something for you.&#xA;Celebrate open source contributors The articles posted in this series are only possible thanks to contributors and project maintainers and so I would like to shout out and thank those folks who really do power open source and enable us all to build on top of what they have created.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #10</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-10/</guid>
      <description>March 9th - Instalment #10 Another bumper packed edition of everything new and interesting in the world where open source and AWS comingle. I have been asked a few times as to how do I choose the articles that go into these posts, so I thought I would very quickly share that; what does and does not go into these posts.&#xA;The idea of this series is to provide a curated list of open source projects that are either created by AWS, by the builders within AWS and open source projects that are created by customers and builders that either help other customers use AWS services and open source projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #9 - Dart, Quarkus, Firecracker and much more</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-9---dart-quarkus-firecracker-and-much-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-9---dart-quarkus-firecracker-and-much-more/</guid>
      <description>As we head into March and instalment #9 of AWS open source news and updates, over the past two months I have shared eight posts covering over 100 unique articles on open source and AWS. It is great to see so much activity and across such a broad spectrum of interests. This instalment is representative of that, with everything from security, machine learning, big data and analytics to new programming runtimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #8</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-8/</guid>
      <description>Another episode of the open source news and updates from AWS, and in this installmant I talk a little about the recent trip to Lagos, Nigeria where I talked about why developers should care about open source at the Open Source Festival, as well as more of the usual updates from around the AWS services catalog as well as some interesting customer projects.&#xA;Open Source Fesitval - Lagos, Nigeria Last week I was invited to speak at the Open Source Festival in Lagos, Nigeria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #7 - networking, data analytics, security and more </title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-7---networking-data-analytics-security-and-more-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-7---networking-data-analytics-security-and-more-/</guid>
      <description>Episode #7 of the open source news and updates for AWS. More security posts in this weeks updates, together with some other cool updates from machine learning, networking and data analytics. I am always looking for interesting open source projects that run on AWS, so if you are working on or know about any, please let me know as I would love to make more people aware.&#xA;Open Distro for ElasticSearch This tweet announced that the AWS managed Amazon Elasticsearch service had now incorporated the security features that have been available on the Apache 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #6 - keep up to date with everything that is happening.</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-6---keep-up-to-date-with-everything-that-is-happening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-6---keep-up-to-date-with-everything-that-is-happening/</guid>
      <description>With still so much to digest post FOSDEM, SustainOSS and CHAOSS, this weeks updates are a little more lightweight and easy to consume. I am going to work on some tutorials/coding posts so would be interested (use comments) on what open source AWS projects you would like to see material on.&#xA;Modernising with open source Following on from the previous post on the essential open source tools for serverless, I came across this blog post by Matt Billock called &amp;ldquo;Essential Open Source Serverless Tools&amp;rdquo; - it is a great reference guide, so check it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #5</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-5/</guid>
      <description>So, hello February and welcome to open source updates and news at AWS #5, the FOSDEM edition. Sadly I was unable to attend due to my passport being held to get a VISA, but I have managed to speak with a number of attendees and get some updates from the event.&#xA;CHAOSCON and SustainOSS The day before FOSDEM we had Sustain Open Source, an event thinking about the sustainability of open source software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #4</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-4/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to open source updates and news at AWS #4 the end of January 2020 edition. Keeping you up to speed with all things open source and AWS. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in.&#xA;Important announcement If you are using the Amazon Linux AMI (this was launched back in 2010, and then subsequently we released the Amazo Linux 2 AMI in 2017) then you should be aware that this AMI is now end-of-life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #3</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-3/</guid>
      <description>So, welcome to open source updates and news at AWS #3 - I should really try and thing of a more entertaining sequence. Next time perhaps&amp;hellip;&#xA;This update has been inspired by a recent trip away with some colleagues. On the way home, I started talking to the person next to me. He was an SA working on HPC, High Performance Computing, an area that I had read about a tiny amount but something I really didnt know that much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #2 </title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-2-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-2-/</guid>
      <description>This is update #2 of open source at AWS (#1 here), the regular update where I will share updates and interesting content from stuff we are doing as well as sharing interesting projects our customers are working on.&#xA;This post has a bit of a Security theme, with a number of interesting open source related projects and content. But dont worry, there is lots more cool stuff on machine learning and AWS open source projects too, So lets dive straight on in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates  #1</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-1/</guid>
      <description>This is the first in a regular series that will keep you posted on the open source projects, communities and activities that are going on in AWS as well as bringing you some interesting open source projects that builders have put together and that I have stumbled across.&#xA;Open Source projects of the week A few open source projects caught my eye, and I havent not yet had a chance to try them out yet, they are on my weekend project todo list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>open source @ reInvent 2019 </title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/open-source--reinvent-2019-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/open-source--reinvent-2019-/</guid>
      <description>So, with reInvent drawing to close and many of the attendees recovering from the after party (re:Play), I thought I would put together a curated list of the open source sessions that have been running this week.&#xA;We had a great variety of open source sessions, covering topics from data and data analytics to robotics. If you missed these sessions, you can check out the videos in this post below. They are sorted by category to help you find those that are of most interest to you.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
