<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amazon SageMaker on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/amazon-sagemaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon SageMaker on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/amazon-sagemaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting gnarly with AI - a quick look at Griptape, an enterprise ready alternative to LangChain</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/getting-started-with-griptape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/getting-started-with-griptape/</guid>
      <description>Getting started with Griptape Getting gnarly with AI&#xA;When I was much much younger, I was known to (very occasionally) drop an ollie, kick-turn, or very occasionally dare a drop in on my trusty skateboard. Thanks to the grip tape, my shoes would stick to the board, and gave me the confidence I could try these tricks. I was always grateful to that grip tape and who knew all these years later, I would become re-aquatinted with it (albeit in a different form!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Amazon CodeWhisperer as my scripting sidekick</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/code-whisperer-my-trusted-sidekick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/code-whisperer-my-trusted-sidekick/</guid>
      <description>How are you using these new AI coding assistants like Amazon CodeWhisperer? I want to share a quick story about how I am finding some success with using these tools, which I hope will encourage you to experiment for yourselves.&#xA;As I work on new projects, demos, blog posts, I often need to do supporting activities such as creating or cleaning up AWS environments, which I sometimes do by hand but mostly do via the AWS CLI or via Python scripts and boto3.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
