<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Firecracker on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/firecracker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Firecracker on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/firecracker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #169</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-169/</guid>
      <description>August 14th, 2023 - Instalment #169 Welcome to #169 of the AWS open source newsletter, featuring the latest and greatest open source news, projects, videos, and community content that you need to know about. Featured in this weeks edition we have more great projects, including a new ODBC driver for Amazon Timestream database, a nice tool to simplify your ssh tunnelling, an essential VSCode extension for working with Cedar policies, a couple of projects that help you shift left and validate / monitor your policies, a solution to help you monitor your Apache Kafka environments, as well as some great sample applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #141</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</guid>
      <description>January 16th, 2023 - Instalment #141 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #141.&#xA;This week we have more new projects for you to practice your four freedoms, including &amp;ldquo;distributed-compute-on-aws-with-cross-regional-dask&amp;rdquo;, a solution to simplify distributed compute using Dask, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-serverless-image-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool to verify your Amazon EMR custom container images, &amp;ldquo;serverless-run-watch&amp;rdquo; a tool to help accelerate your local development if you are using the Serverless Framework, &amp;ldquo;aws-sso-auto-expand-accounts&amp;rdquo; a quick browser extension for those using AWS SSO, &amp;ldquo;basti&amp;rdquo; a cool Bastion Host alternative, &amp;ldquo;klotho&amp;rdquo; generate cloud native code from your code, &amp;ldquo;amazon-route53-hosted-zone-sync&amp;rdquo; a nice solution for hybrid DNS use cases, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #138</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-138/</guid>
      <description>December 12th, 2022 - Instalment #138 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #138. After a week off due to re:Invent, this edition is packed with content on many of the open source related announcements. As always, we have a great line up of new projects for you to practice your four freedoms on. In no particular order, we have projects like &amp;ldquo;eks-node-viewer&amp;rdquo;, a nice visualisation tool for your Amazon EKS clusters, &amp;ldquo;pg_tle&amp;rdquo; a great new project to make your PostgreSQL environments safer, &amp;ldquo;dyna53&amp;rdquo; a fun project that finally turns Amazon Route 53 into a database, &amp;ldquo;dynamodb-mass-migrations&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you migrate to Amazon DynamoDB, &amp;ldquo;visual-asset-management-system&amp;rdquo; a very nice digital asset management tool, &amp;ldquo;fast-differential-privacy&amp;rdquo; implement differential privacy in your PyTorch models, &amp;ldquo;migration-hadoop-to-emr-tco-simulator&amp;rdquo; a handy total cost of ownership calculator for Amazon EMR, &amp;ldquo;realtime-toxicity-detection&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you stay on top of your online communities, &amp;ldquo;functionclarity&amp;rdquo; a very cool tool to check the integrity of your serverless functions before executing, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #134</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-134/</guid>
      <description>November 7th, 2022 - Instalment #134 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #134. This weeks newsletter was featured in the latest Build on Open Source on twitch.tv/aws, so I hope some of you were able to tune in and watch.&#xA;New projects that we featured include &amp;ldquo;enclaver&amp;rdquo;, a toolkit to make working with enclaves easier, &amp;ldquo;s3crets_scanner&amp;rdquo; a new secrets scanning tool, &amp;ldquo;sandbox-accounts-for-events&amp;rdquo; a way to easily vend temporary environments, &amp;ldquo;frontend-discovery&amp;rdquo; helps you define and drive adoption of a frontend discovery patterns, &amp;ldquo;cf-sam-openapi-file-organization-demo&amp;rdquo;, a tool to help you get started with API development, &amp;ldquo;decoupling-microservices-lambda-amazonmq-rabbitmq&amp;rdquo; a sample solution to get you started on how to use micro services with RabbitMQ, &amp;ldquo;how-to-write-more-correct-software-workshop&amp;rdquo; a workshop to get you developing better software, and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #132</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-132/</guid>
      <description>October 21st, 2022 - Instalment #132 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #132. This newsletter was covered in last Friday&amp;rsquo;s Build on Open Source, so if you missed it, don&amp;rsquo;t worry as you can view episode five of Build on Open Source. In this episode special guest Abhishek Gupta walked us through how to use cdk8s using Golang, building a Wordpress site in minutes.&#xA;New projects this week include &amp;ldquo;duvet&amp;rdquo; a tool to help honour RFC in code, &amp;ldquo;aws-lambda-explorer&amp;rdquo; a gui tool to explore your AWS Lambda functions, &amp;ldquo;k3s-aws-terraform-cluster&amp;rdquo; deploy k3s on AWS via Terraform, &amp;ldquo;snow-transfer-tool&amp;rdquo; a tool to help you transfer data via Snowball devices, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-vscode-toolkit&amp;rdquo; a new VSCode plugin for Amazon EMR users, &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-for-discourse&amp;rdquo; a quick way to deploy the open source discourse tool, &amp;ldquo;image-optimization&amp;rdquo; a reference example of how to do image optimising, and &amp;ldquo;gtfs-serverless-ticketing-sample&amp;rdquo; a sample application using public transport data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #127</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-127/</guid>
      <description>September 16th, 2022 - Instalment #127 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter, edition #127. I hope some of you were able to catch Derek and myself sharing a peek at this edition, and enjoyed as our special guest, AWS Hero Ian Mckay walked us through some of his open source projects. It was very cool indeed, and if you have not yet watched, Ian shares an early glimpse of a new project - so make sure you check that out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #123</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-123/</guid>
      <description>August, 5th, 2022 - Instalment #123 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter episode #123.&#xA;I sometimes speak with builders who are experienced developers but perhaps new to open source. A common question I get asked is what the impact of them working on open source might be on their careers. Whilst it is never a guarantee, open source can be a great career accelerator. I was reminded of that last week when reading the excellent post from Ran Isenberg, who shared his experience in his post How One Open-Source Code Donation Got Me Promoted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #112</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-112/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-no-112/</guid>
      <description>May 13th, 2022 - Instalment #112 Newsletter #112.&#xA;Welcome to this weeks round up of AWS open source news. This weeks new projects features projects such as &amp;ldquo;aws-dataall&amp;rdquo; an open source framework for building a data marketplace, &amp;ldquo;backpack&amp;rdquo; a set of tools to help you work with the AWS Panorama devices, and we have other projects that help you automate DNS tasks, manage game servers, automate data ingestion, and more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
