<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pulumi on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</title>
    <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/pulumi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pulumi on Beachgeek blog - a refuge for pineapple on pizza lovers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/tags/pulumi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #143</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-143/</guid>
      <description>January 30th, 2023 - Instalment #143 Welcome to edition #143 of the AWS open source newsletter, and another week of great new open source projects for you to try out. This week we feature projects including &amp;ldquo;aws-cdk-in-electron&amp;rdquo;, a project that lets you put AWS CDK in a graphical user interface, &amp;ldquo;lightsail-k8s-installer&amp;rdquo; that helps you deploy Kubernetes into Amazon Lightsail, &amp;ldquo;porting-advisor-for-graviton&amp;rdquo; a great project to help you migrate to Arm based AWS Graviton instance types, &amp;ldquo;aws-ebook-downloader&amp;rdquo; a browser tool to help you easily download pdf&amp;rsquo;s on AWS topics, &amp;ldquo;lake-formation-permissions-sync&amp;rdquo; a useful tool to help you keep on top of your Lake Formation setups, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source newsletter #141</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-141/</guid>
      <description>January 16th, 2023 - Instalment #141 Welcome&#xA;Welcome to the AWS open source newsletter of 2023, edition #141.&#xA;This week we have more new projects for you to practice your four freedoms, including &amp;ldquo;distributed-compute-on-aws-with-cross-regional-dask&amp;rdquo;, a solution to simplify distributed compute using Dask, &amp;ldquo;amazon-emr-serverless-image-cli&amp;rdquo; a tool to verify your Amazon EMR custom container images, &amp;ldquo;serverless-run-watch&amp;rdquo; a tool to help accelerate your local development if you are using the Serverless Framework, &amp;ldquo;aws-sso-auto-expand-accounts&amp;rdquo; a quick browser extension for those using AWS SSO, &amp;ldquo;basti&amp;rdquo; a cool Bastion Host alternative, &amp;ldquo;klotho&amp;rdquo; generate cloud native code from your code, &amp;ldquo;amazon-route53-hosted-zone-sync&amp;rdquo; a nice solution for hybrid DNS use cases, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS open source news and updates #119</title>
      <link>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.beachgeek.co.uk/newsletter/aws-open-source-news-and-updates-119/</guid>
      <description>July 1st, 2022 - Instalment #119 Welcome to regular and new readers alike, to the AWS open source newsletter episode #119.&#xA;This week we feature more new open source projects, such as &amp;ldquo;cdk-bill-bot&amp;rdquo;, a tool that can help you reduce AWS bill surprises, &amp;ldquo;steampipe-mod-aws-perimeter&amp;rdquo; helps you look for resources that are publicly accessible, &amp;ldquo;aws-cloudformation-diagrams&amp;rdquo; is a nice visualisation tool for CloudFormation users, &amp;ldquo;aws-swagger-ui&amp;rdquo; a project to help you set up Swagger UI for API Gateway, &amp;ldquo;kinesis-hot-shard-advisor&amp;rdquo; a handy tool that helps you identify whether you have hot key or hot shard issues on your Kinesis data streams, and many more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
